<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<Database>
  <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_NEW_PSYCHIATRY_TREATMENTS">
    <LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
    <Contributors>
      <Name>banishee</Name>
    </Contributors>
    <LocalizedStrings>
        <GameDBLocalizedString>
            <LocID>TRT_INTRAMUSCULAR_INJECTION_OF_VITAMIN_B12</LocID>
            <Text>Intramuscular Injection of Vitamin B12</Text>
        </GameDBLocalizedString>
        <GameDBLocalizedString>
            <LocID>TRT_INTRAMUSCULAR_INJECTION_OF_VITAMIN_B12_DESC</LocID>
            <Text>This product is an anti-anemic agent. Vitamin B12 is involved in methyl conversion and folate metabolism in the body, promoting the conversion of 5-methyltetrahydrofolate to tetrahydrofolate. Its deficiency leads to impaired DNA synthesis, affecting the maturation of red blood cells. This product also promotes the conversion of methylmalonic acid to succinic acid, participating in the tricarboxylic acid cycle. This action is related to the synthesis of myelin lipids and the maintenance of the functional integrity of myelinated nerve fibers. Neurological damage in Vitamin B12 deficiency may be related to this. It is mainly used for megaloblastic anemia caused by a lack of intrinsic factor, and can also be used as an adjuvant treatment for subacute combined degeneration of the nervous system, such as neuritis.\n\nRequired Departments: Hematology, Neurology Medical Center.</Text>
        </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_HEM_INTRATHECAL_INJECTION_METHOTREXATE</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Intrathecal Injection of Methotrexate</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_HEM_INTRATHECAL_INJECTION_METHOTREXATE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Methotrexate (MTX) is injected directly into the subarachnoid space via lumbar puncture, allowing it to diffuse into the cerebrospinal fluid and quickly reach an effective therapeutic concentration. Methotrexate inhibits dihydrofolate reductase, thereby interfering with DNA synthesis, repair, and cell replication. It thus possesses broad-spectrum anti-tumor activity and can be used alone or in combination with other chemotherapy drugs. It is also used to treat severe, recalcitrant, disabling psoriasis that is unresponsive to conventional therapies. The intrathecal injection of dexamethasone + methotrexate and/or cytarabine is the recommended regimen for the treatment of central nervous system leukemia.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
          <GameDBLocalizedString>
            <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_TCM_JINGLING_ORAL_LIQUIDS</LocID>
            <Text>Jingling Oral Liquid</Text>
          </GameDBLocalizedString>
          <GameDBLocalizedString>
            <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_TCM_JINGLING_ORAL_LIQUIDS_DESC</LocID>
            <Text>Jingling Oral Liquid, with ingredients including Radix Rehmanniae Praeparata, Rhizoma Dioscoreae, Poria, Cortex Moutan, Rhizoma Alismatis, Radix Polygalae, Os Draconis, Fructus Ligustri Lucidi, Cortex Phellodendri Chinensis, Rhizoma Anemarrhenae (salt-processed), Fructus Schisandrae Chinensis, and Rhizoma Acori Tatarinowii, can subdue yin to nourish yang, calm the mind and improve intelligence. It is used for attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) in children, manifesting as inattention, hyperactivity, talkativeness, impulsivity, willfulness, learning difficulties, a red tongue, and a thready, rapid pulse, which are signs of kidney yin deficiency and ascendant liver yang.\n\nRequired Department: Psychiatry.</Text>
          </GameDBLocalizedString>
          
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_BETAHISTINE</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Betahistine</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_BETAHISTINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Betahistine, formerly known as Antivertigo, is a diamine oxidase inhibitor. It has a significant vasodilatory effect on cerebral and cardiovascular vessels, especially the vertebrobasilar artery system, improving blood circulation and lowering systemic blood pressure. Additionally, it increases cochlear and vestibular blood flow, alleviating inner ear vertigo, tinnitus, and aural fullness. It also increases capillary permeability, promotes the absorption of extracellular fluid, and eliminates endolymphatic hydrops. Furthermore, it has antithrombotic and mild diuretic effects. It is primarily used for Meniere's disease, vascular headaches, and cerebral arteriosclerosis, and can also be used to treat acute ischemic cerebrovascular disease. It is also effective for postural vertigo and tinnitus caused by conditions such as hypertension. Common formulations of betahistine include betahistine hydrochloride oral solution and betahistine mesylate tablets.\n\nRequired Department: Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_FLUNARIZINE</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Flunarizine</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_FLUNARIZINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Flunarizine, trade name Sibelium, is a non-selective calcium channel blocker. It prevents excessive transmembrane calcium ion entry into cells, thus avoiding intracellular calcium overload. It also prevents massive calcium influx into neurons during ischemia and hypoxia, improves cerebral microcirculation and neuronal metabolism, and inhibits cerebral vasospasm, platelet aggregation, and increased blood viscosity. Additionally, it has a cell membrane-stabilizing effect. Flunarizine is indicated for the prophylactic treatment of migraine and the symptomatic treatment of vertigo caused by vestibular disorders. Caution is advised, as Flunarizine is contraindicated in patients with a history of depression, Parkinson's disease, or symptoms of other extrapyramidal disorders.\n\nRequired Department: Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_GINKGO_BILOBA_BEXTRACT</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Ginkgo Biloba Extract</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_GINKGO_BILOBA_BEXTRACT_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Ginkgo Biloba Extract, generally referred to as EGb 761, trade name Tanakan, is primarily used for cerebral and peripheral circulatory disorders. This drug can scavenge excessive free radicals in the body and inhibit lipid peroxidation of cell membranes, thereby protecting them from various damages caused by free radicals. It has a regulatory effect on the circulatory system, maintaining the tone of arteries and veins by stimulating the release and inhibiting the degradation of catecholamines, as well as stimulating the production of prostaglandins and endothelium-derived relaxing factor to induce arterial dilation. It improves hemodynamics by reducing whole blood viscosity and enhancing the plasticity of red and white blood cells, thereby improving blood circulation. It also has a tissue-protective effect, increasing the supply of oxygen and glucose to ischemic tissues and increasing the number of certain neurotransmitter receptors, such as muscarinic, norepinephrine, and serotonin receptors.\n\nRequired Department: Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_METOCLOPRAMIDE</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Intramuscular Injection of Metoclopramide</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_METOCLOPRAMIDE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Metoclopramide, with trade names like Reglan or Maxolon, primarily exerts its potent central antiemetic effect by antagonizing dopamine D2 receptors. It acts on the dopamine receptors in the chemoreceptor trigger zone of the medulla oblongata, thereby raising its threshold.\n\nRequired Department: Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
        
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_MIDAZOLAM</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>(Class I Psychotropic) Continuous Intravenous Infusion of Midazolam</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_MIDAZOLAM_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Midazolam, trade name Dormicum, is a short-acting benzodiazepine and a central nervous system depressant. It has hypnotic and sedative effects with a rapid onset and short duration of action, as well as anxiolytic, anticonvulsant, and muscle-relaxant properties. Its intramuscular or intravenous injection is indicated for pre-surgical sedation, anxiolysis, and amnesia. Intravenous injection is used for diagnostic, therapeutic, and endoscopic procedures, as well as for the induction of general anesthesia before the administration of other anesthetic agents. Its continuous intravenous infusion is used as an anesthetic for sedation in intubated and mechanically ventilated patients, or for sedation in critical care. According to the "Announcement on Adjusting the Catalog of Psychotropic Drugs" (2024, No. 54) by the NMPA, Ministry of Public Security, and NHC, Midazolam injection is now a Class I psychotropic drug.\n\nRequired Department: Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_NSAIDS_IBUPROFEN</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Ibuprofen</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_NSAIDS_IBUPROFEN_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Ibuprofen inhibits prostaglandin synthesis, thus possessing antipyretic, analgesic, and anti-inflammatory effects. It is used to relieve mild to moderate pain, such as headache, joint pain, migraine, toothache, muscle pain, neuralgia, and dysmenorrhea. It is also used for fever associated with the common cold or influenza. Common formulations of ibuprofen include regular tablets, sustained-release tablets, chewable tablets, granules, and suspensions.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
        
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_PARACETAMOL_AND_CAFFEINE_TABLETS</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Paracetamol and Caffeine Tablets</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_PARACETAMOL_AND_CAFFEINE_TABLETS_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Paracetamol and Caffeine Tablets are a compound formulation consisting of paracetamol and caffeine. Paracetamol produces antipyretic and analgesic effects by inhibiting prostaglandin synthesis. Caffeine is a central nervous system stimulant that constricts cerebral blood vessels, reducing the amplitude of their pulsation. This medication is used for fever caused by the common cold or influenza and for the relief of mild to moderate pain.\n\nRequired Department: Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_PHYSICAL_COOLING</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Physical Cooling</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_PHYSICAL_COOLING_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Physical cooling refers to methods such as applying ice packs or alcohol baths to rapidly lower the body temperature.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
        
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_PRIMIDONE</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Primidone</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_PRIMIDONE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Primidone, formerly known as Mysoline, is an antiepileptic drug. Its major metabolite in the body is phenobarbital, and they work together to exert their effect. It is indicated as monotherapy or adjunctive therapy for tonic-clonic seizures, simple partial seizures, and complex partial seizures. It is also used to treat essential tremor and senile tremor.\n\nRequired Department: Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_SUMATRIPTAN</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Sumatriptan</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_SUMATRIPTAN_DESC</LocID>                                          	
        <Text>Sumatriptan is a specific therapeutic agent indicated for the acute treatment of migraine attacks. It is a selective agonist for vascular 5-HT1D receptors, acting on the human basilar artery and the vasculature of the dura mater to cause vasoconstriction.\n\nRequired Department: Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_PSYCHOTHERAPY</LocID>
        <Text>Psychotherapy (Social psychological interventions)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_PSYCHOTHERAPY_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>In the fields of psychiatry and clinical psychology, psychotherapy refers to a therapeutic approach based on talk therapy guided by psychological principles. It involves a process of interpersonal interaction where a socially recognized therapist helps an individual who is struggling with psychological distress or is unable to fully function.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_REPETITIVE_BREATHING_THERAPY</LocID>
        <Text>Repetitive breathing therapy</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_REPETITIVE_BREATHING_THERAPY_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Repetitive breathing therapy is an effective method for alleviating hyperventilation. This therapy primarily involves the use of a paper cone or similar device placed over the patient's mouth and nose to increase the concentration of carbon dioxide (CO₂) during respiration. By doing so, it helps counteract respiratory alkalosis, thereby reducing symptoms associated with over-breathing.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_PSYCHOSTIMUALNTS_MODAFINIL</LocID>
        <Text>Modafinil</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString> 
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_PSYCHOSTIMUALNTS_MODAFINIL_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Modafinil is a novel non-amphetamine central nervous system stimulant primarily used for the treatment of various types of excessive sleepiness disorders, such as narcolepsy, obstructive sleep apnea, and shift work sleep disorder. Compared to traditional stimulants, it generally has milder side effects. However, long-term use still carries a potential risk of drug dependence.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_PSYCHOSTIMUALNTS_METHYLPHENIDATE</LocID>
        <Text>Methylphenidate</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_PSYCHOSTIMUALNTS_METHYLPHENIDATE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Methylphenidate, also known as piperidine methyl ester and commercially available as Concerta (extended-release) and Ritalin (immediate-release), is a central nervous system stimulant. It acts directly on the brain to enhance cortical activity, improve mental alertness, alleviate fatigue, and boost overall mental energy. It is used to manage symptoms of attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) and excessive daytime sleepiness related to narcolepsy. </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_NRIS_TOMOXETINE</LocID>
        <Text>Atomoxetine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_NRIS_TOMOXETINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Atomoxetine, marketed under the brand name Strattera, is a non-stimulant medication used to treat attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD). Specifically, it is a selective norepinephrine reuptake inhibitor (NRI). Atomoxetine is non-addictive and provides effects that are either slightly less potent than or comparable to those of stimulants like methylphenidate. It has demonstrated efficacy and good tolerance over a one-year follow-up period. Initially found to be effective in adults, Atomoxetine was later approved for use in children aged 6 years and older.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BZs_ALPRAZOLAM</LocID>
        <Text>Alprazolam</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BZs_ALPRAZOLAM_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Alprazolam is a benzodiazepine of the 3-benzodiazepine class, characterized by its medium duration and potency. It provides rapid and potent anxiolytic, sedative, and hypnotic effects. Research has also indicated that Alprazolam may possess some antidepressant properties. While benzodiazepines are known for their rapid onset, reliability, and efficacy, long-term or improper use can lead to addiction, dependence, and misuse.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BZs_LORAZEPAM</LocID>
        <Text>Lorazepam</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BZs_LORAZEPAM_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Lorazepam, also known as Lora, is a medium-to-short-acting benzodiazepine with potent anxiolytic and hypnotic effects. It is recognized for having one of the strongest anxiolytic effects among benzodiazepines, and it also provides sedative benefits. Lorazepam offers several advantages, including rapid onset of action, safety, and efficacy. However, prolonged or improper use can lead to dependence, addiction, and misuse. In addition to its use in treating anxiety disorders, lorazepam is also commonly used for managing agitation and tension in conditions such as schizophrenia.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BZs_DIAZEPAM</LocID>
        <Text>Diazepam</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BZs_DIAZEPAM_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Diazepam, also known as Valium, is a long-acting, medium-potency benzodiazepine with the typical benzodiazepine properties of anxiolytic, sedative-hypnotic, and antiepileptic effects. Diazepam is valued for its rapid onset, safety, and effectiveness. However, like other benzodiazepines, it poses risks of dependence, addiction, and misuse with prolonged or improper use. Additionally, diazepam is frequently used in the management of alcohol withdrawal.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
        <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIHYPERTENSIVE_PRAZOSIN</LocID>
        <Text>Prazosin</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIHYPERTENSIVE_PRAZOSIN_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Prazosin was originally developed as a traditional antihypertensive medication. However, in recent years, it has been discovered to have significant efficacy in treating nightmares, particularly those associated with post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD). Clinical practice and several research studies have demonstrated that doses of 2 to 6 mg of prazosin can effectively reduce the frequency and severity of nightmares in individuals with PTSD. </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_MOOD_STABILIZER_LITHIUM</LocID>
        <Text>Lithium salts (lithium carbonate)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_MOOD_STABILIZER_LITHIUM_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Lithium salts have various forms and exert complex physiological and pharmacological effects on the brain. The primary lithium compound used in clinical treatment is lithium carbonate, classified as a mood stabilizer. Lithium's broad and effective long-term benefits make it a widely used treatment option for bipolar disorder.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_HALOPERIDOL</LocID>
        <Text>Haloperidol</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_HALOPERIDOL_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Haloperidol is a high-potency typical (first-generation) antipsychotic medication from the butyrophenone class, noted for its strong D2 receptor antagonism. It is highly effective in treating the positive symptoms of schizophrenia, including hallucinations, delusions, and agitation. Additionally, it is used for managing manic symptoms and behavioral disturbances, such as those associated with Tourette syndrome in children. Due to its side effect profile, particularly the risk of EPS and cardiac issues, haloperidol use has become less common in favor of newer antipsychotics with a more favorable side effect profile.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_OLANZAPINE</LocID>
        <Text>Olanzapine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_OLANZAPINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Olanzapine is a derivative of clozapine and is classified as a second-generation antipsychotic. It is a multi-receptor antagonist that blocks 5-HT2A, D2, D1, and D4 receptors, as well as muscarinic cholinergic receptors (M1), H1 histamine receptors, 5-HT3 receptors, and α1 adrenergic receptors. Its blockade of 5-HT2A receptors is approximately eight times more potent than its blockade of dopamine receptors. Although its pharmacological profile is similar to clozapine, olanzapine has a significantly lower risk of agranulocytosis. Common dose-related adverse effects include sedation, weight gain, and increased appetite, which are considered metabolic side effects.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
    <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SSRIS_FLUVOXAMINE</LocID>
        <Text>Fluvoxamine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SSRIS_FLUVOXAMINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Fluvoxamine is a selective serotonin reuptake inhibitor (SSRI) that is approved for the treatment of depression and obsessive-compulsive disorder (OCD). Clinically, among SSRIs, fluvoxamine is noted for its particularly effective treatment of OCD.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SSRIS_PAROXETINE</LocID>
        <Text>Paroxetine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SSRIS_PAROXETINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Paroxetine, marketed under the brand name Paxil, is a selective serotonin reuptake inhibitor (SSRI). Clinically, it is used to treat depression, particularly major depressive disorder with anxiety, as well as generalized anxiety disorder, panic disorder, and obsessive-compulsive disorder.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
   
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SSRIS_ESCITALOPRAM</LocID>
        <Text>Escitalopram</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SSRIS_ESCITALOPRAM_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Escitalopram, commonly known under the brand name Lexapro, is the oxalate salt form of escitalopram. It is the S-enantiomer of citalopram and exhibits a serotonin reuptake inhibition effect that is approximately 5 to 7 times stronger than that of citalopram. As a selective serotonin reuptake inhibitor (SSRI), escitalopram is primarily used in clinical practice for the treatment of depression.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SSRIS_FLUOXETINE</LocID>
        <Text>Fluoxetine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SSRIS_FLUOXETINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Fluoxetine, commonly known by the brand name Prozac, is available in the form of fluoxetine hydrochloride capsules. It is an antidepressant that belongs to the class of selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors (SSRIs). Fluoxetine is widely recognized as the first SSRI to be marketed and is primarily used for the treatment of depression. Additionally, it is used as an adjunctive therapy for the treatment of bulimia nervosa and for various other mental disorders, including obsessive-compulsive disorder (OCD).</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SNRIS_DULOXETINE</LocID>
        <Text>Duloxetine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SNRIS_DULOXETINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Duloxetine is a phenylamine compound and a serotonin-norepinephrine reuptake inhibitor (SNRI). First synthesized in the 1980s, it is used in the treatment of depression, generalized anxiety disorder, and chronic musculoskeletal pain. It is contraindicated for use in combination with monoamine oxidase inhibitors (MAOIs), as well as with other SSRIs and SNRIs.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_MECT</LocID>
        <Text>MECT</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_MECT_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Modified Electroconvulsive Therapy (MECT) is a treatment method that involves inducing a generalized seizure with a small amount of electrical current under general anesthesia and with the support of oxygenation. It is primarily used for the treatment of major depressive episodes, but it can also be employed for mood disorders, schizophrenia, and for the treatment of neuroleptic malignant syndrome or serotonin syndrome induced by antipsychotic or antidepressant medications.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_SLEEPING_DRUGS_ZS_ESZOPICLONE</LocID>
        <Text>Eszopiclone</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_SLEEPING_DRUGS_ZS_ESZOPICLONE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Eszopiclone is the right-handed isomer of zopiclone and is a non-benzodiazepine cyclopyrrolone-class sedative-hypnotic. It is the first medication approved for long-term use to improve both sleep onset and sleep maintenance difficulties. It demonstrates effective treatment for insomnia in both adults and elderly patients, with a rapid onset of action and efficacy lasting up to 6 hours. Eszopiclone is well-tolerated, with no rebound insomnia or withdrawal symptoms upon discontinuation. Possible side effects include dry mouth, dizziness, and drowsiness.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANXIOLYTIC_TANDOSPIRONE</LocID>
        <Text>Tandospirone</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANXIOLYTIC_TANDOSPIRONE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Tandospirone is an azapirone-class anxiolytic medication with a stronger serotonergic effect compared to buspirone. It is used to treat anxiety states associated with various neuroses, such as generalized anxiety disorder, and other conditions accompanied by anxiety. Unlike benzodiazepines or antipsychotics, tandospirone operates through a different mechanism of action, and does not produce sedative, muscle relaxant, or anticonvulsant effects. Its side effects are generally milder.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEMENTIA_MEDICINE_DONEPEZIL</LocID>
        <Text>Donepezil</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEMENTIA_MEDICINE_DONEPEZIL_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Donepezil (brand name: Aricept) is a cholinesterase inhibitor with potential cognitive-enhancing effects. It is commonly used in clinical practice for the treatment of Alzheimer's disease and various types of dementia.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
  
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_TCM_SHUGAN_JIEYU_CAPSULES</LocID>
        <Text>Shu Gan Jie Yu capsules</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_TCM_SHUGAN_JIEYU_CAPSULES_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Shu Gan Jie Yu capsules is an important compound preparation made from Hypericum perforatum and Eleutherococcus senticosus. It is used to soothe the liver, relieve depression, strengthen the spleen, and calm the mind. It is indicated for mild to moderate unipolar depression with symptoms of liver qi stagnation and spleen deficiency.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_TCM_WULING_CAPSULES</LocID>
        <Text>Wu Ling capsules </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_TCM_WULING_CAPSULES_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Wu Ling capsules are a pure traditional Chinese medicine formulation derived from the rare medicinal fungus Pachyma (Wu Ling Shen) using modern biotechnology. The capsules contain adenosine, polysaccharides, sterols, various amino acids, vitamins, and trace elements, and are effective in treating anxiety and depression. They have sedative and calming properties and are indicated for conditions such as insomnia, depressive and anxious states, migraines, and neuroses.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_INTRAVENOUS_INFUSION_OF_SULPIRIDE</LocID>
        <Text>Intravenous infusion of Sulperazone</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_INTRAVENOUS_INFUSION_OF_SULPIRIDE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Sulperidone is a benzamide-class antipsychotic medication that can be administered via intravenous infusion to help alleviate symptoms of acute psychosis. However, it is prone to recurrence, often requiring multiple doses to maintain its effects, and it is generally less effective compared to Modified Electroconvulsive Therapy (MECT).</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BZs_CLONAZEPAM_IV</LocID>
        <Text>Intravenous infusion of Diazepam</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BZs_CLONAZEPAM_IV_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Diazepam is a benzodiazepine medication. Intravenous injection can rapidly alleviate panic attacks and relieve anxiety states. However, it is crucial to administer it slowly to avoid the risk of respiratory depression.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BZs_CLONAZEPAM</LocID>
        <Text>Clonazepam</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BZs_CLONAZEPAM_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Clonazepam is a potent benzodiazepine with anxiolytic, sedative, hypnotic, and anticonvulsant properties. Benzodiazepines are known for their rapid onset, reliability, and effectiveness; however, long-term or inappropriate use may lead to addiction, dependence, and abuse. Anecdotal evidence suggests that clonazepam may be effective for depersonalization, potentially by preventing sleep deprivation and promoting sleep. It may also address symptoms such as derealization, déjà vu, and reduced attention in depersonalization. Additionally, it is used in the treatment of refractory tic disorders.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_MOOD_STABILIZER_lAMOTRIGINE</LocID>
        <Text>Lamotrigine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_MOOD_STABILIZER_lAMOTRIGINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Lamotrigine is traditionally known as an antiepileptic drug, but it has also emerged as a mood stabilizer, particularly effective for the depressive phase of bipolar disorder. Additionally, there is anecdotal evidence suggesting that lamotrigine may be effective in treating depersonalization, potentially alleviating symptoms such as derealization, somatic depersonalization, and attentional disturbances associated with the condition.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BETA_BLOCKERS_PROPRANOLOL</LocID>
        <Text>Propranolol</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BETA_BLOCKERS_PROPRANOLOL_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Propranolol is a beta-blocker used to treat various arrhythmias, hypertension, and tremors. In the field of psychiatry, while propranolol has minimal direct effects on anxiety itself, it can alleviate the physical and physiological symptoms of anxiety, such as palpitations and tremors. As a result, it is sometimes used to manage performance anxiety in social phobia or social anxiety disorder, though its efficacy for generalized anxiety disorder remains a subject of debate.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_QUETIAPINE</LocID>
        <Text>Quetiapine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_QUETIAPINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Quetiapine is a versatile second-generation antipsychotic with high affinity for 5-HT2, H1, 5-HT6, α1, and α2 receptors, moderate affinity for D2 receptors, and very low affinity for D1, M1, and D4 receptors. While its efficacy in treating positive symptoms of schizophrenia is relatively weak, it has a more pronounced effect on negative symptoms. Additionally, quetiapine is noted for its significant anxiolytic effects among atypical antipsychotics, with extensive research supporting its efficacy. It is also used in the treatment of refractory insomnia and can enhance the effects of antidepressants. It may have some benefit in alleviating agitation in individuals with intellectual disabilities.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SSRIS_SERTRALINE</LocID>
        <Text>Sertraline</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SSRIS_SERTRALINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Sertraline is a selective serotonin reuptake inhibitor (SSRI) with antidepressant, anxiolytic, and anti-obsessive properties. Due to its relatively low incidence of adverse effects, it is frequently used in children, adolescents, and older adults, particularly for symptoms associated with organic mental disorders.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BRAIN_FUNCTION_IMPROVEMENT_DRUGS_PIRACETAM</LocID>
        <Text>Oxiracetam</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BRAIN_FUNCTION_IMPROVEMENT_DRUGS_PIRACETAM_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Oxiracetam is a nootropic drug classified as a new-generation cognitive enhancer. It works by promoting the synthesis of phosphatidylcholine and phosphatidylethanolamine, thereby increasing the ATP/ADP ratio in the brain. This action enhances protein and nucleic acid synthesis, which in turn improves brain metabolism. Oxiracetam is used to counteract brain function damage and memory impairment caused by physical and chemical factors. It has been shown to improve retrograde amnesia due to hypoxia and may enhance memory and learning functions in patients with various types of senile dementia and memory disorders.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_AWAKENING_PROMOTING_DRUGS_PITOLISANT</LocID>
        <Text>Tilopidine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_AWAKENING_PROMOTING_DRUGS_PITOLISANT_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Tilopidine is a recently approved selective histamine H3 receptor inverse agonist. By inhibiting the negative feedback mechanism, it increases histamine release and activates histaminergic neurons, resulting in an arousal effect. As a novel and potent wakefulness-promoting agent, tilopidine has not shown significant addiction potential to date.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_ARIPIPRAZOLE</LocID>
        <Text>Aripiprazole</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_ARIPIPRAZOLE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Aripiprazole is an atypical antipsychotic and is considered the only third-generation antipsychotic currently available. It functions as a unique serotonin-dopamine activity modulator. Aripiprazole exhibits partial agonistic effects on post-synaptic dopamine D2 receptors, and when dopamine (DA) activity is elevated, it helps reduce DA activity to alleviate positive symptoms of schizophrenia. Aripiprazole is indicated for the treatment of schizophrenia and has recently gained widespread recognition for its efficacy in treating Tourette's disorder, particularly Tourette's syndrome. The drug is noted for its effectiveness and relatively mild side effect profile, including minimal sedation and a low incidence of extrapyramidal symptoms or hyperprolactinemia.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_SHAOMA_ZHIJING_GRANULES</LocID>
        <Text>Shaoma Zhijing granules</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_SHAOMA_ZHIJING_GRANULES_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Shaoma Zhijing Granules are composed of Bai Shao (white peony root), Tianma (Gastrodia elata), Shizi (spiny jujube), Gou Teng (Uncaria), Lingzhi (Reishi mushroom), He Shou Wu (Polygonum multiflorum), Suan Zao Ren (Sour Jujube Seed), Cu Wu Wei Zi (vine tea), Zhi Zi (Gardenia), Dan Nan Xing (Fritillaria), and Huang Qin (Scutellaria). This formulation is used for treating Tourette's syndrome from the perspective of traditional Chinese medicine, where it is believed to address conditions of liver wind stirring and internal phlegm-heat disturbance.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIEPILEPTICS_TOPIRAMATE</LocID>
        <Text>Topiramate</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIEPILEPTICS_TOPIRAMATE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Topiramate, marketed under the brand name Topamax, is an anticonvulsant medication used primarily for the treatment of epilepsy. In pediatric psychiatry, it is utilized as a treatment option for refractory tic disorders.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_XIAOER_ZHILI_SYRUP</LocID>
        <Text>Xiao'er Zhili syrup</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_XIAOER_ZHILI_SYRUP_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Xiao'er Zhili Syrup is a traditional Chinese medicine composed of ingredients such as tortoise shell (Gui Jia), dragon bone (Long Gu), Polygala (Yuan Zhi), Acorus (Shi Chang Pu), and rooster comb (Xiong Ji). This formulation is used to enhance cognitive function, nourish the heart and kidneys, and calm the mind. It is specifically indicated for children with attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) associated with heart and kidney deficiency and phlegm-damp obstruction.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_NICOTINE_CHEWING_GUM</LocID>
        <Text>Nicotine chewing gum</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_NICOTINE_CHEWING_GUM_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Nicotine Chewing Gum is a nicotine replacement therapy product that incorporates nicotine into chewing gum. When chewed, the gum gradually releases nicotine, which is then absorbed through the oral mucosa into the bloodstream. The specific usage involves chewing one piece of gum whenever the urge to smoke arises. This method helps alleviate withdrawal symptoms associated with quitting smoking, such as cravings, increased appetite, irritability, anxiety, and difficulties with concentration.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_VARENICLINE</LocID>
        <Text>Varenicline</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_VARENICLINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Varenicline significantly increases smoking cessation rates and reduces cravings, urges, and the satisfaction derived from smoking among those who have relapsed. Varenicline has a high affinity and selectivity for the α4β2 nicotinic acetylcholine receptors in neurons, exhibiting both agonistic and antagonistic properties. It acts as an agonist by binding to these receptors, stimulating dopamine release, which helps alleviate cravings and withdrawal symptoms associated with smoking cessation. Simultaneously, its antagonistic effect prevents nicotine from binding to the receptors, reducing the pleasure of smoking and the urge to smoke, thereby lowering the likelihood of relapse.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_NDRIS_BUPROPION</LocID>
        <Text>Bupropion</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_NDRIS_BUPROPION_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Bupropion is a novel antidepressant whose pharmacological mechanism remains somewhat controversial. It can be classified as a norepinephrine and dopamine reuptake inhibitor (NDRI). Bupropion has antidepressant effects but lacks anxiolytic properties, making it commonly used for treating depression and smoking cessation.  However, it may lead to central nervous system activation symptoms, with insomnia being one of the most common adverse effects. Anxiety and depression may also occur.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_AGOMELATINE</LocID>
        <Text>Agomelatine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_AGOMELATINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>In psychiatry, agomelatine is the first antidepressant that acts on melatonin receptors. Agomelatine likely exerts its antidepressant effects by activating the MT1 and MT2 receptors, which helps synchronize circadian rhythms. Additionally, agomelatine is an antagonist at the 5-HT2C receptor, which blocks the receptor's inhibitory effect on norepinephrine (NE) and dopamine (DA) release, thereby increasing their concentrations in the prefrontal cortex and contributing to its antidepressant properties. In the field of sleep medicine, agomelatine has the ability to regulate circadian rhythms and sleep cycles. It effectively improves sleep continuity and increases the proportion of slow-wave sleep, leading to a normalization of overnight slow-wave and delta wave distribution, thereby enhancing overall sleep quality without altering REM sleep. Overall, patients generally tolerate agomelatine well, with no significant withdrawal symptoms observed.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BRAIN_FUNCTION_IMPROVEMENT_DRUGS_NIMODIPINE</LocID>
        <Text>Nimodipine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_BRAIN_FUNCTION_IMPROVEMENT_DRUGS_NIMODIPINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Nimodipine is a cerebrovascular agent and one of the most widely used neuroprotective drugs in clinical practice. It readily crosses the blood-brain barrier and acts on cerebral blood vessels and neuronal cells, selectively dilating cerebral vessels without causing "steal" phenomena. Nimodipine also antagonizes various factors contributing to cerebral vasospasm, including K+, 5-HT, arachidonic acid, hydrogen peroxide, TXA2, PGF2α, and vasospasm following subarachnoid hemorrhage.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_TCM_TIANZHI_GRANULES</LocID>
        <Text>Tianzhi granules</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_TCM_TIANZHI_GRANULES_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Tianzhi Granules consist of a combination of Gastrodia Elata, Uncaria Rhynchophylla, Fossilia Ossis Chinensis, Eucommia Ulmoides, Taxillus Chinensis, Poria Cocos, Fallopia Multiflora, Sophora Japonica, Gardenia Jasminoides, Scutellaria Baicalensis, Achyranthes Bidentata, and Leonurus Japonicus. This formulation is designed to calm the liver and subdue yang, nourish the liver and kidneys, and enhance cognitive function. It is used for treating cognitive decline, poor memory, slowed thinking, and disorientation resulting from liver yang rising, along with symptoms such as dizziness, headaches, irritability, insomnia, bitter mouth, dry throat, and lower back and knee weakness. This remedy is indicated for mild to moderate vascular dementia associated with liver yang rising syndrome.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_MOOD_STABILIZER_SODIUM_VALPROATE</LocID>
        <Text>Sodium valproate</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_MOOD_STABILIZER_SODIUM_VALPROATE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Sodium valproate (brand name: Divalproex) is an anticonvulsant and mood stabilizer used in the treatment of manic episodes in bipolar disorder, particularly effective for rapid cycling and mixed episodes. Its efficacy in preventing relapse of bipolar disorder is comparable to that of lithium, making it a suitable alternative to lithium. Additionally, sodium valproate is commonly used for managing and treating behavioral symptoms associated with dementia, such as euphoria that impacts daily functioning.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_DPD_ACETYLCYSTEINE</LocID>
        <Text>N-acetylcysteine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_DPD_ACETYLCYSTEINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>N-acetylcysteine (NAC) is primarily used as a mucolytic agent, facilitating the breakdown of mucus. In psychiatric settings, it has been noted, anecdotally, to be effective for treating symptoms of depersonalization, particularly emotional numbing. The proposed mechanism for this effect involves NAC’s potential to modulate the glutamatergic system. While ketamine, which is an NMDA receptor antagonist, can induce depersonalization-like symptoms, NAC acts as a glycine-NMDA receptor agonist. This agonistic action may theoretically help improve depersonalization by counteracting the NMDA receptor blockade induced by ketamine.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_OTHER_NEW_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_MIRTAZAPINE</LocID>
        <Text>Mirtazapine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_OTHER_NEW_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_MIRTAZAPINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Mirtazapine is the only new antidepressant with strong antihistaminic effects, which helps in sedation and appetite stimulation. Similar to tricyclic antidepressants and SSRIs, mirtazapine is also a potent REM sleep suppressant, which can reduce nighttime awakenings and extend total sleep duration. The most common side effects of mirtazapine include excessive sedation, increased appetite, weight gain, and dry mouth.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SARIS_TRAZODONE</LocID>
        <Text>Trazodone</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SARIS_TRAZODONE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Trazodone is the first of the second-generation antidepressants. Its primary pharmacological effect is mediated through postsynaptic 5-HT2 receptors. Although it has weak effects on the 5-HT transporter, Ach receptors, and H1 receptors, these can be considered negligible. It does not have significant activity on NE and DA receptors but is an antagonist at peripheral α-adrenergic receptors, which can lead to side effects such as orthostatic hypotension, dizziness, dry mouth, and priapism. Trazodone is a choice for the acute treatment of depression, demonstrating efficacy comparable to that of tricyclic antidepressants (TCAs) and other new antidepressants. It also helps improve sleep, with its sedative effects potentially providing rapid relief for patients with severe insomnia or anxiety. The most common side effect of trazodone is drowsiness.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_RISPERIDONE</LocID>
        <Text>Risperidone</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_RISPERIDONE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Risperidone, a second-generation antipsychotic introduced after clozapine, is now available in a long-acting injectable formulation. It exhibits strong antagonistic effects on central 5-HT receptors, particularly 5-HT2A, and on D2 receptors. Its antagonistic effect on D2 receptors is similar to that of haloperidol. Additionally, risperidone has high affinity for α1 and α2 receptors but lower affinity for β receptors and muscarinic cholinergic receptors. Consequently, it shares similar efficacy with typical antipsychotics in treating positive symptoms of schizophrenia while also showing good effectiveness for negative symptoms. Risperidone has minimal sedative effects and lacks significant anticholinergic side effects.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
     <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ORAL_APPLIANCE</LocID>
        <Text>Oral appliances</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ORAL_APPLIANCE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Oral appliances, commonly referred to as "snoring devices," are a popular non-surgical treatment option for sleep-disordered breathing, particularly in adults with mild to moderate obstructive sleep apnea (OSA) and primary snoring. They are favored for their simplicity, effectiveness, and cost-efficiency. However, careful consideration is needed to assess whether the patient has temporomandibular joint disorders. These appliances come in various designs, including soft palate retainers, tongue retainers, and mandibular advancement devices. The latter, due to its potential to alter dental and skeletal structures, is contraindicated in patients whose dental and skeletal development is not yet complete, such as in adolescents.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_CPAP</LocID>
        <Text>CPAP</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_CPAP_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Continuous Positive Airway Pressure (CPAP) therapy is the preferred treatment for moderate to severe obstructive sleep apnea-hypopnea syndrome (OSAHS), with its long-term efficacy well established. CPAP delivers a continuous stream of air at a prescribed pressure to keep the airway open, effectively reducing the duration of sleep apnea and hypopnea events, correcting oxygen desaturation, and reducing respiratory effort-related arousals. This results in improved daytime alertness, cognitive function, memory, and attention, as well as better management of associated metabolic abnormalities and cardiovascular complications, ultimately enhancing the patient's quality of life. </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_FERROUS_SULFATE</LocID>
        <Text>Ferrous sulfate</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_FERROUS_SULFATE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Ferrous sulfate is a commonly used iron supplement for treating iron deficiency anemia caused by chronic blood loss, nutritional deficiencies, or conditions such as pregnancy and developmental stages in children. Additionally, because iron supplementation can improve the pathological state of iron deficiency in the brain associated with restless legs syndrome (RLS), it is also commonly used as adjunctive therapy for RLS.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_VITAMIN_C</LocID>
        <Text>Vitamin C</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_VITAMIN_C_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Vitamin C plays a crucial role in antibody and collagen formation, tissue repair (including certain redox reactions), metabolism of phenylalanine, tyrosine, and folate, utilization of iron and carbohydrates, synthesis of fats and proteins, and maintenance of immune function. It is also essential for the hydroxylation of serotonin, maintaining vascular integrity, and enhancing the absorption of non-heme iron. Vitamin C is commonly used for dietary supplementation, chronic dialysis, prevention and treatment of vitamin C deficiency, acidifying urine, and idiopathic erythrocytosis. Additionally, vitamin C can enhance iron absorption when used in conjunction with iron supplements.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_LEVODOPA_AND_BENSERAZIDE_HYDROCHLORIDE</LocID>
        <Text>Cabergoline</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_LEVODOPA_AND_BENSERAZIDE_HYDROCHLORIDE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Cabergoline is a combination formulation of levodopa and benserazide. Levodopa, a precursor in dopamine synthesis, can cross the blood-brain barrier and is used to increase dopamine levels in the brain, making it effective for treating Parkinson's disease, which is characterized by a deficiency of dopamine in the basal ganglia. Additionally, cabergoline can be used for treating restless legs syndrome, potentially due to its effect on normalizing dopaminergic abnormalities in the central nervous system. However, long-term use may exacerbate symptoms, so it should be administered only as needed. The levodopa component of the combination can cause gastrointestinal adverse effects, cardiovascular adverse effects, dyskinesias (involuntary movements), and psychiatric disorders.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_PRAMIPEXOLE</LocID>
        <Text>Pramipexole</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_PRAMIPEXOLE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Pramipexole is a non-ergot, selective dopamine receptor agonist that specifically stimulates dopamine D2 receptors, with minimal action on D1 receptors and low affinity for adrenergic α2 receptors. It is commonly used in the treatment of Parkinson's disease. Due to its long half-life, pramipexole does not require nighttime dosing and is well-tolerated with minimal complications during long-term use. It effectively alleviates over 90% of symptoms in restless legs syndrome (RLS), making it a first-line treatment option for RLS, with pramipexole being the only approved medication for this condition. Initial treatment may be associated with orthostatic hypotension and gastrointestinal adverse effects.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTICHOLINERGICS_TRIHEXYPHENIDYL</LocID>
        <Text>Benztropine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTICHOLINERGICS_TRIHEXYPHENIDYL_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Benztropine is an anticholinergic medication that selectively blocks cholinergic neural pathways in the striatum while exerting minimal peripheral effects. This action helps restore the balance between dopamine and acetylcholine in the brain. It is used in the treatment of Parkinson's disease, Parkinsonism, and drug-induced extrapyramidal disorders. In other words, benztropine can counteract the extrapyramidal side effects caused by typical antipsychotic medications.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_TCAs_CLOMIPRAMINE</LocID>
        <Text>Clomipramine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_TCAs_CLOMIPRAMINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Clomipramine, also known as Anafranil, is a traditional tricyclic antidepressant. Due to its broad spectrum of side effects, it is now infrequently used for depression and is primarily considered a second-line treatment option for obsessive-compulsive disorder (OCD).</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_TIAPRIDE</LocID>
        <Text>Sulpride</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIPSYCHOTIC_DRUG_TIAPRIDE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Sulpride, marketed as Thiapride, is a traditional benzamide antipsychotic that is not approved in Canada, the United States, or the United Kingdom but is more commonly used in Europe and China. It primarily acts as a dopamine antagonist, mainly targeting the midbrain and limbic system. Sulpride is used for conditions such as Tourette syndrome, chorea, and geriatric psychosis. Common side effects include drowsiness, gastrointestinal reactions, and dizziness or fatigue. It has a lower incidence of extrapyramidal side effects and may cause moderate, transient hyperprolactinemia. Notably, it does not affect cognitive functions or neurophysiological parameters in children, nor does it interfere with the hypothalamic-pituitary regulation of various hormones.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_CALCIUM_CHANNEL_REGULATOR_PREGABALIN</LocID>
        <Text>Pregabalin</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_CALCIUM_CHANNEL_REGULATOR_PREGABALIN_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Pregabalin is a calcium channel modulator and an anticonvulsant medication. It is commonly used to treat various types of neuropathic pain and chronic pain conditions. Additionally, it is considered a first-line treatment for generalized anxiety disorder (GAD).</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_REPLACEMENT_THERAPY_METHADONE</LocID>
        <Text>Methadone</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_REPLACEMENT_THERAPY_METHADONE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Methadone is a synthetic opioid and a typical μ-opioid receptor agonist, similar to morphine. It has effects such as analgesia, respiratory depression, miosis, and sedation, and long-term use can lead to dependence. Methadone is characterized by its convenience (oral administration, once daily), long half-life, high doses that can block the euphoric effects of heroin, and stable absorption and bioavailability. It is commonly used as a detoxification treatment for opioid dependence. Methadone is also classified as a narcotic drug.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_REPLACEMENT_THERAPY_BUPRENORPHINE</LocID>
        <Text>Buprenorphine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_REPLACEMENT_THERAPY_BUPRENORPHINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Buprenorphine is a semi-synthetic derivative of thebaine and is classified as a partial opioid receptor agonist. It primarily activates the μ-opioid receptor, which helps manage withdrawal symptoms, and also acts on the κ-opioid receptor while antagonizing the δ-opioid receptor. Buprenorphine is more potent than pethidine and morphine in terms of analgesic effect, but has a lower potential for dependence compared to morphine. However, long-term use can still lead to dependence. </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_TCM_YIAN_HUISHENG_ORAL_LIQUIDS</LocID>
        <Text>Yi'an Huisheng oral liquid</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_TCM_YIAN_HUISHENG_ORAL_LIQUIDS_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Yi'an Huisheng Oral Liquid, composed of Red Ginseng, Prepared Aconite, Cinnamon, Cardamom, Schisandra, Angelica Sinensis, White Peony Root, Cyperus Rotundus, Processed Corydalis, Scorpion, Salvia Miltiorrhiza, Fried Ziziphus Jujuba, and Licorice, is used for warming and tonifying the spleen and kidneys, calming the mind, and detoxifying. It is applied to alleviate withdrawal symptoms in individuals with opioid addiction, specifically those with a pattern of spleen and kidney yang deficiency.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_COMPOUND_FLUPENTIXOL_AND_MELITRACEN_TABLETS</LocID>
        <Text>Fluphenazine-Melitracen tablets</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_COMPOUND_FLUPENTIXOL_AND_MELITRACEN_TABLETS_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Fluphenazine-Melitracen Tablets is a combination medication that includes a typical antipsychotic (fluphenazine) and a tricyclic antidepressant (melitracen). It is approved for the treatment of mild to moderate depression and anxiety symptoms, including traditional neurotic disorders or neuroticism, and is used for various functional somatic symptoms or psychosomatic disorders, such as irritable bowel syndrome, functional dyspepsia, chronic gastritis, and cardiac neurosis. The medication is known for its relatively rapid onset of action. However, it is considered to have limited long-term efficacy and may cause serious adverse effects, such as tardive dyskinesia, and significant withdrawal reactions. Therefore, it is not recommended as a routine medication for depression, anxiety disorders, or similar conditions in major clinical guidelines.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      </LocalizedStrings>
  </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
