<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<Database>
  <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_NEW_PSYCHIATRY_DIAGNOSES">
   <LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
    <Contributors>
      <Name>liebesalt</Name>
    </Contributors>
    <LocalizedStrings>
    
    <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_SCHIZOPHRENIA</LocID>
        <Text>Schizophrenia</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_SCHIZOPHRENIA_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Schizophrenia is serious mental disorder. According to China Epidemiologic Survey in 1993, the lifetime prevalence of schizophrenia is 0.655%, and it is one of the most prevalent mental illnesses. The onset of schizophrenia is mostly insidious. The majority of patients have their first onset between teenage to their 30s, having either intermittent or persistent episodes. Patients with recurrent episodes may have personality changes and impaired social functioning. It is generally believed that the onset of schizophrenia is related to a combination of physical, genetic, psychological and environmental factors. Subtypes of schizophrenia include hebephrenic, catatonic, disorganized, etc.. Some categorize schizophrenia according to symptoms: Positive (e.g. hallucinations, delusions) and negative (e.g. emotion changes, unintelligible speech). </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
    
    <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_OBSESSIVE-COMPULSIVE_DISORDER</LocID>
        <Text>Obsessive-compulsive disorder (OCD)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_OBSESSIVE-COMPULSIVE_DISORDER_DESC</LocID>

        <Text>Obsessive-compulsive disorder (OCD), is a neurological disorder characterized by recurrent and persistent obsessive concepts governing obsessive-compulsive behaviors. Patients experience uncontrollable and recurring thoughts (obsessions), engages in repetitive behaviors (compulsions), or both. Patients knows that they are meaningless, unnecessary, and redundant, and the patient has a strong desire to get rid of them, but is unable to control them, thus feeling distressed. The lifetime prevalence rate of OCD worldwide ranges from 0.9% to 3.0%. Pre-adolescence and early adulthood are the peak periods for the onset of OCD. Many patients with OCD also experience comorbidity with anxiety disorders, tic disorders, complicating their treatments. </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
    
    <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_PTSD</LocID>
        <Text>Post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_PTSD_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD), refers to an unusual threatening or catastrophic psychological trauma, resulting in the delayed onset of a long-term persistent psychiatric disorder. The onset could develop from days to years after the trauma. Formerly known as delayed psychosomatic responses, PTSD was thought to exist primarily among veterans, prisoners of war, and survivors of concentration camps, but has since expanded to include the general population who have suffered shocking, scary, or dangerous events. Personality, coping styles, social support, physical condition, and family history of mental disorders, are important factors that influence the condition and course of the illness. PTSD may also exhibit symptoms similar to those of depression, including repeated recurrence and avoidance of traumatic experiences, and persistent hypervigilance. Some may experience comorbidity with depression.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
    
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_MAJOR_DEPRESSIVE_DISORDER</LocID>
        <Text>Major Depressive Disorder (MDD)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_MAJOR_DEPRESSIVE_DISORDER_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Major depressive disorder (MDD) is a common type of depressive disorder. It is characterized by pervasive low mood, low self-esteem, and loss of interest or pleasure in normally enjoyable activities. Patients often experience abnormal feelings of guilt and hopelessness, and may engage in suicidal behavior as a result.In addition, physical symptoms, such as sleep disorders, loss of appetite, weight loss, constipation, body pain and discomfort, loss of sexual desire, autonomic nervous system dysfunction, and cognitive symptoms, manifesting certain level of cognitive decline. Extreme cases may even exhibit neurodegenerative disorder symptoms similar to dementia, know as depressive pseudodementia.  Monoamine deficiency hypothesis is one of a major hypothesis explaining the cause of depression. </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_BIPOLAR_DISORDER</LocID>
        <Text>Bipolar Disorder</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_BIPOLAR_DISORDER_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Bipolar disorder is a mood disorders in which patients' moods shift unsually between mania and depression episodes. There are 2 types of bipolar disorder. Bipolar I disorder, in which manic and depressive episodes are both present, each lasting for at least 7 days; Bipolar II disorder is defined by a pattern of depressive episodes and hypomanic episodes. Typical clinical symptoms include mania, depression, racing thoughts, mood swings, changes in behavior, and in severe cases, other psychotic symptoms such as hallucinations and delusions. During a manic attack episode, patients may even engage in impulsive or risky behaviors.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_GENERALIZED_ANXIETY_DISORDER</LocID>
        <Text>Generalized Anxiety Disorder (GAD)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_GENERALIZED_ANXIETY_DISORDER_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Generalized Anxiety Disorder (GAD) is a mental condition characterized by persistent and excessive worry or anxiety about a wide range of situations and events. Patients with GAD often experience an overwhelming sense of unease, tension, and apprehension, even when there is little or no apparent reason for concern. Patients with GAD may also exhibit symptoms such as frequent sadness and crying, although this does not necessarily indicate a depressed mood; rather, it may be a response to their underlying anxiety and distress. It is often co-morbid with other somatic disorders, including pain syndromes, hypertension, cardiovascular disease, and gastrointestinal disorders. The pathogenesis of GAD includes genetics, childhood experiences, personality, stressful life events, and neurobiological factors. </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
     <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_CHRONIC_INSOMNIA</LocID>
        <Text>Chronic insomnia</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_CHRONIC_INSOMNIA_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Chronic insomnia, a prevalent sleep disorder, encompasses persistent and frequent difficulties in falling asleep or maintaining sleep. The prevalence of insomnia varies due to differences in its definition, ranging from 4% to 48%. Among patients diagnosed with insomnia, 31% to 75% are identified as having chronic insomnia. The primary symptoms of insomnia disorder include dissatisfaction with sleep quality despite suitable sleep environment, characterized by difficulty falling asleep, frequent awakenings, and early morning awakening. These symptoms significantly impact daytime functioning, leading to fatigue, reduced energy , difficulty concentrating, decreased memory, irritability, and low mood. Patients often experience anxiety regarding their sleep patterns. Chronic insomnia is frequently comorbid with other sleep disorders, such as sleep-related breathing disorders and restless leg syndrome. Additionally, insomnia may be associated with the use, misuse, or abuse of certain substances.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_PANIC_ATTACK</LocID>
        <Text>Panic attack</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_PANIC_ATTACK_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Panic attacks are intense episodes of sudden and overwhelming fear or discomfort that typically reach their peak within minutes, with about 20% of individuals experiencing at least one panic attack in their lifetime. These attacks can occur unexpectedly and repeatedly, causing a wide range of distressing physical and psychological symptoms. During these episodes, individuals often experience pronounced cardiovascular and respiratory symptoms such as palpitations, chest tightness, shortness of breath, numbness, dizziness, and intense sweating. In severe cases, they may feel as if they are facing imminent death or insanity. Some may also experience depersonalization and hyperventilation symptoms. Due to the severity of these physical symptoms, panic attacks are often misdiagnosed as conditions like heart disease. Without timely intervention, individuals with panic attacks may experience recurring attacks in the following week or weeks, with some even occurring daily, leading to constant worry about future attacks. This state of affairs can persist for several months or even years.
		</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
       <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ALCOHOL_WITHDRAWAL</LocID>
        <Text>Alcohol withdrawal</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ALCOHOL_WITHDRAWAL_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Alcohol withdrawal syndrome, also known as alcohol detoxification or withdrawal, occurs when individuals abruptly reduce or stop alcohol consumption after prolonged heavy drinking. This syndrome encompasses a range of symptoms resulting from the body's reaction to the absence of alcohol. Alcohol is a central nervous system depressant and a widely recognized addictive substance. Consequently, sudden cessation of alcohol intake can lead to a cascade of physical and psychological symptoms, including tremors, sweating, nausea, anxiety, palpitations, fever, vomiting, and, in severe cases, seizures and hallucinations. Delirium tremens, a severe and potentially life-threatening manifestation of alcohol withdrawal, may also occur. Without proper medical management, it can result in serious complications such as dehydration, electrolyte imbalances, even death.
		</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_INS</LocID>
        <Text>Transient insomnia</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
	  
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_SOICAL_ANXIETY_DISORDER</LocID>
        <Text>Social anxiety disorder (SAD)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_SOICAL_ANXIETY_DISORDER_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Social anxiety disorder is a common anxiety disorder. Primary symptoms include a significant and persistent fear of social situations that may induce embarrassment or awkwardness. Individuals experiencing this condition often feel overwhelmed and avoid making eye contact, leading to severe anxiety responses. While patients are aware of the irrationality of their fears, they struggle to manage them, resulting in efforts to avoid various social settings to prevent embarrassment. This avoidance behavior significantly impacts their personal, professional, and social lives. Onset typically occurs during adolescence, Comprising of 10% to 20% individuals with anxiety disorders. The etiology and mechanisms of social anxiety disorder are associated with biological and psychosocial factors.
		</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ALZHEIMER_DISEASE</LocID>
        <Text>Alzheimer's disease</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ALZHEIMER_DISEASE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Alzheimer's disease is a chronic neurodegenerative disorder with a subtle onset and progressive development. It is clinically characterized by cognitive impairments such as memory loss, aphasia, apraxia, agnosia, and executive dysfunction. Additionally, patients may exhibit psychiatric and behavioral abnormalities, as well as a decline in social functioning. In severe cases, individuals with Alzheimer's may not recognize their family memebers' or even their own name and age. They may struggle to communicate with simple words, experience incontinence, difficulties in eating, and spend most of their time in bed. Many patients suffer from malnutrition, pulmonary infections, or bedsores within two years of becoming bedridden. Alzheimer's disease is prevalent among the elderly, with research indicating a prevalence of 2% to 5% among individuals aged 65 and above. While its etiology is complex and its pathogenesis not fully understood, diagnosis typically relies on differential diagnoses, although certain laboratory tests such as ECG, neuroimaging, and cerebrospinal fluid analysis can assist in the diagnosis of Alzheimer's.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
     <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ADHD</LocID>
        <Text>Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ADHD_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) is a neurodevelopmental disorder and a common behavioral problem in childhood. Often referred to as hyperactivity, patients exhibit disproportionate inattention, excessive activity, emotional instability, and impulsivity, which negatively impact their social, family, and academic functioning. Despite often having normal or near-normal intelligence, individuals with ADHD may struggle academically, partly due to impaired executive functions. While previously thought to be solely caused by attention deficits or hyperactivity, recent research has revealed varying degrees of perceptual motor deficits as another contributing factor to learning difficulties. The prevalence of ADHD is repoted to be between 3% and 5%, and it is recognized as a chronic condition with lifelong impacts, requiring lifelong intervention. About 70% of symptoms persist into adolescence, with 30% to 50% of patients experiencing lifelong symptoms. The etiology of ADHD is complex and remains unclear to date, although it is primarily believed to result from the combined influence of genetic and environmental factors.
		</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ADJUSTMENT_DISORDER</LocID>
        <Text>Adjustment disorder</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ADJUSTMENT_DISORDER_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>
		Adjustment disorder is a short-term and mild state of distress and emotional imbalance that occurs during significant life changes or environmental transitions, such as starting school, bereavement, or experiencing a serious illness. It often involves some degree of behavioral changes but does not manifest psychotic symptoms. The onset of the disorder is typically within three months of a stressful event, with prevalence higher among adults but possible at any age. Symptoms of adjustment disorder vary widely, primarily characterized by emotional and behavioral abnormalities, including anxiety, irritability, depressive mood, timidity, difficulty concentrating, confusion, feeling overwhelmed, and irritability. Patients may also experience physical symptoms such as palpitations and tremors. While individuals may exhibit tendencies toward maladaptive or impulsive behaviors, such occurrences are rare. Occasionally, patients may engage in alcohol or substance abuse, but more severe symptoms are uncommon.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_BARCOLEPSY</LocID>
        <Text>Narcolepsy</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_BARCOLEPSY_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Narcolepsy with cataplexy is characterized by uncontrollable episodes of sudden sleepiness, sudden collapse, sleep paralysis, hallucinations, and disrupted nighttime sleep, representing a central nervous system disorder. Patients often experience irresistible sleep attacks or muscle weakness episodes, even collapsing. Sleep paralysis can occur during falling asleep or waking up, where patient is consciousness but cannot move or speak. The cause of narcolepsy is generally believed to be a combination of environmental and genetic factors. Many cases are preceded by triggers such as emotional stress, mental pressure, or excessive fatigue, while upper respiratory infections may also induce narcoleptic episodes.  Differential diagnosis involves distinguishing narcolepsy from obstructive sleep apnea, idiopathic hypersomnia, epilepsy, and other disorders.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ANOREXIA_NERVOSA</LocID>
        <Text>Anorexia nervosa</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ANOREXIA_NERVOSA_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Anorexia nervosa is a eating disorder influenced by various genetic, neurobiological, imaging, social, familial factors. Individuals with anorexia nervosa experience anxiety related to weight and pathological fear of obesity. Behaviorally, they consciously maintain a significantly low calorie intake, striving to achieve extreme weight loss goals through irrational means. They may restrict the quantity and variety of food consumed, reduce carbohydrate intake, limit meat and protein consumption, and excessively focus on the fat, calorie, and sugar content of foods. They may also eliminate nutritious foods from their diet. They may also engage in compulsive physical activities, including excessive exercise and chores beyond their physical capabilities. Additionally, they may resort to purging methods and misuse of medications such as laxatives, diuretics, and diet pills, leading to physiological dysfunction. These behaviors often result in damage to various bodily systems, including cardiac arrhythmias, hypotension, and amenorrhea, potentially leading to death.
		</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_TIC_DISORDERS</LocID>
        <Text>Tic disorders</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_TIC_DISORDERS_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Tic disorders, including Tourette's syndrome, chronic motor or vocal tic disorders, and transient tic disorders ,are neurodevelopmental disorders characterized by involuntary movements. They are common disorders among children and adolescents. Reports show that transient tic disorder affects 5% to 20% of school-age children, while the prevalence of chronic tic disorder during childhood and adolescence ranges from 1% to 2%. The occurrence of Tourette's Syndrome is between 0.05% and 3%, higher in males. They often lead to low self-esteem, impaired learning performance, and adaptation difficulties. Symptoms may worsen with stress, anxiety, fatigue, excitement, or fever, and can be alleviated by relaxation, engagement in an activity, or sleep. Additionally, many individuals with tic disorders have comorbid OCD, ADHD, and other conditions. Some develop self-harm behaviors, mood disorders, sleep disorders, and migraines.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_TOBACCO_WITHDRAWAL</LocID>
        <Text>Tobacco withdrawal</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_TOBACCO_WITHDRAWAL_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Tobacco withdrawal refers to the abrupt stop or reduction of tobacco use after regular use for weeks, causing withdrawal symptoms within the next 24 hours. Nicotine, the primary component of tobacco, stimulates the adrenal medulla at low doses, leading to the release of adrenaline, which reflexively causes respiratory stimulation, vasoconstriction, increased blood pressure, and increased cardiovascular burden through the stimulation of carotid and aortic chemoreceptors. At high doses, it exhibits initial excitation of nerve cells followed rapidly by inhibition. Individuals undergoing tobacco withdrawal experience intense cravings for tobacco, along with symptoms such as decreased heart rate and blood pressure, increased saliva production, headaches, insomnia, irritability, anxiety, lack of concentration, and even mood depression. Nicotine dependence, like drug dependence, is a chronic relapsing brain disorder.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_SPECIFIC_PHOBIA</LocID>
        <Text>Specific Phobia</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_SPECIFIC_PHOBIA_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>
		Specific phobia, also known as simple phobia, is a subtype of phobia characterized by an irrational fear of certain objects, creatures, situations, or activities. Individuals with specific phobias experience anticipatory anxiety, fear-induced anxiety, and avoidance behaviors to alleviate their anxiety. They often fear the consequences of encountering these objects rather than the objects themselves. For example, they may avoid sharp objects out of fear of harming others or fear being bitten by various small animals. While most patients recognize their fears as excessive and irrational, they struggle to control them, causing distress. Common types of specific phobia in clinical practice include animal phobia, natural environment phobia, claustrophobia, and blood-injection-injury phobia. The six-month prevalence rate of specific phobia in English-speaking countries ranges from 5% to 12% according to reports, with surveys indicating an annual prevalence rate of 10% to 11.3% in the US.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_AGORAPHOBIA</LocID>
        <Text>Agoraphobia</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_AGORAPHOBIA_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>
		Agoraphobia is a type of anxiety disorder characterized by a fear of specific places or situations. In English-speaking countries, the prevalence of agoraphobia ranges from 2.9% to 6.7%. Individuals with agoraphobia may fear crowded places such as auditoriums or theaters, public transportation like buses, subways, or airplanes, leaving home alone, or even being alone at home. The main clinical feature is anxiety experienced by patients in places where it's difficult to quickly leave or escape, often accompanied by panic attacks or without them. When entering such places, patients feel nervous and experience symptoms like dizziness, palpitations, chest tightness, sweating, and in severe cases, derealization or fainting. Due to intense fear, insecurity, or distress, patients often engage in avoidance behaviors. After one or more experiences, anticipatory anxiety may develop, causing patients to feel anxious or avoidant whenever encountering similar situations. The presence of a companion may alleviate or eliminate the fear for some patients, leading to dependence on others when going out.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_SHIFT_WORK_SLEEP_DISORDER</LocID>
        <Text>Shift Work Sleep Disorder (SWSD)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_SHIFT_WORK_SLEEP_DISORDER_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Shift Work Sleep Disorder (SWSD) refers to a disruption in the sleep-wake cycle due to the inconsistency between an individual's work schedule and the typical work hours, resulting in insomnia and excessive daytime fatigue. This disorder is commonly experienced by night shift, early morning shifts, or rotating shifts workers. Working during times when one should be sleeping, particularly during nighttime shifts, leads to drowsiness during work hours, insomnia after work, insufficient sleep compensation, and disruption of nervous system. While not all shift workers develop this disorder, a prevalence of 2% to 5% among night shift or rotating shift workers is estimated, with some reports as high as 10% to 38% in industrialized countries. Age, gender, exposure to sunlight or timing of exposure, and individual sleep or work habits contribute to the susceptibility and onset, while the mechanisms involve disturbances in the sleep-wake cycle, chronic irregular sleep deprivation, and disruptions in melatonin secretion. Clinical assessment methods involve sleep diaries or actigraphy.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_NIGHT-EATING_SYNDROME</LocID>
        <Text>Night Eating Syndrome (NES)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_NIGHT-EATING_SYNDROME_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Night Eating Syndrome (NES) is a psychiatric disorder characterized by persistent abnormal eating behaviors during the night. This condition is triggered by mental stress, causing hormonal imbalances and is manifested by overeating after dinner, eating upon awakening from sleep, loss of appetite in the morning, sleep disturbances, and other symptoms. Although nocturnal eating may serve as a coping mechanism for stress and emotional issues, this disorder is often associated with other mental health conditions such as depression, anxiety disorders, and sleep disorders. The prevalence of NES ranges from 1.1% to 1.5%. It is higher among obese individuals, ranging from 6% to 16%. The prevalence is even higher in populations with eating disorders, particularly in those with Binge Eating Disorder and Bulimia Nervosa.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_DEPERSONALIZATION</LocID>
        <Text>Depersonalisation disorder (DP)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_DEPERSONALIZATION_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Depersonalisation disorder (DP) is a complex psychological condition characterized by a disruption in the integration of one's consciousness and self-awareness. Individuals often feel like external observers of their own mental processes, experiencing a subjective sense of unreality or detachment from themselves or their surroundings. When this feeling becomes intense, severe, persistent, or recurrent, interfering with daily functioning, it leads to dissociative identity disorder. Roughly 2.4% of the general population meet the diagnostic criteria for DP, and it often coexists with mood, anxiety, and other psychiatric disorders. The disorder is commonly triggered by severe stress, depression, anxiety disorders, and the use of hallucinogens. Cannabis, in some cases, can also induce depersonalisation. Clinically, it's essential to differentiate DP from temporal lobe epilepsy, panic disorder, acute stress disorder, migraines, and other similar conditions.
		</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_OSAHS</LocID>
        <Text>Obstructive sleep apnea-hypopnea syndrome (OSAHS)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_OSAHS_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>
		Obstructive sleep apnea-hypopnea syndrome (OSAHS), formerly known as obstructive sleep apnea, is a sleep disorder characterized by repeated collapse and obstruction of the upper airway during sleep, leading to pauses in breathing and shallow breathing, resulting in frequent episodes of hypoxemia, hypercapnia, significant fluctuations in intra-thoracic pressure, disrupted sleep architecture, increased sympathetic nervous system activity, and long-term damage to multiple organ systems. Clinically, patients often complain of symptoms such as snoring, choking, daytime sleepiness, lack of concentration, and emotional disturbances, increasing the risk of developing conditions like hypertension, ischemic heart disease or stroke, and type 2 diabetes. It involves factors that can interact with each other, such as genetics, anatomical factors, obesity, gender, age, sleep position, nasal resistance, alcohol and smoking habits, medication effects, and other related diseases. OSAHS needs to be differentiated from primary snoring, narcolepsy, among other conditions, though there is a high likelihood of comorbidity between narcolepsy and this syndrome.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ACUTE_STRESS_DISORDER</LocID>
        <Text>Acute stress disorder</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ACUTE_STRESS_DISORDER_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>
		Acute stress disorder is a transient mental disorder caused by sudden and unusually intense stressful life events. The onset of this condition typically occurs within minutes to hours after encountering a significant psychological stressor and lasts for several weeks. The triggering factors for this disorder are typically sudden, extraordinary threats to life or overwhelming traumatic experiences that individuals find difficult to cope with. Symptoms of acute stress disorder vary widely but often include an initial state of confusion, limited consciousness, narrowed attention, and an inability to grasp external stimuli or maintain orientation. In severe cases, individuals may experience loosened thought associations, fragmented hallucinations, delusions, and severe anxiety or depression, leading to what is termed acute stress psychosis. Differential diagnosis is necessary to distinguish acute stress disorder from organic mental disorders, various mood disorders, and dissociative disorders.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ACUTE_AND_TRANSIENT_PSYCHOTIC_DISORDERS</LocID>
        <Text>Acute and transient psychotic disorder</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_ACUTE_AND_TRANSIENT_PSYCHOTIC_DISORDERS_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>
		Acute and transient psychotic disorder is a relatively common mental disorder characterized by the sudden onset of acute symptoms. The condition progresses rapidly, typically transitioning from a state lacking psychotic features to a markedly abnormal psychotic state within two weeks or shorter. Symptoms are vivid, varied, and often dynamic, with rapid remission. Clinically, it bears resemblance to acute episodes of schizophrenia, with prominent hallucinations, delusions, and other positive symptoms. These may manifest as fragmentary delusions, multiple delusions, fragmentary hallucinations, or a variety of hallucinations, often accompanied by disorganized speech, psychomotor agitation, or catatonia, as well as emotional instability. While acute stress is not a fundamental criterion for diagnosis, life events triggering acute stress are often present before the onset of the disorder. The total duration of the illness generally does not exceed three months. Differential diagnosis is necessary to distinguish it from schizophrenia, mood disorders, organic mental disorders, and substance-induced psychiatric disorders.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_RESTLESS_LEGS_SYNDROME</LocID>
        <Text>Restless legs syndrome (RLS)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_RESTLESS_LEGS_SYNDROME_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>
		Restless legs syndrome (RLS), also known as Willis-Ekbom disease, is a prevalent neurological sensory-motor disorder. This condition can occur at any age but tends to increase with age, with women being twice as likely to be affected as men. The syndrome can be classified into two main types: primary RLS and secondary RLS, which is often caused by factors such as iron deficiency, certain medications, pregnancy, or chronic kidney failure. The typical clinical presentation of restless legs syndrome involves a strong, urgent desire to move the limbs, especially during periods of rest or nighttime, leading to discomfort such as tingling, burning, itching, or aching sensations, commonly affecting the legs but potentially extending to other parts of the body. This condition can severely disrupts sleep. Differential diagnosis is essential to distinguish it from conditions such as nocturnal leg cramps, drug-induced akathisia, various types of anxiety disorders, and other organic problems.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_SOMATIC_SYMPTOM_DISORDER</LocID>
        <Text>Somatic symptom disorder</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_SOMATIC_SYMPTOM_DISORDER_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>
		Somatic symptom disorder, characterized by abnormal thoughts, emotional responses, and behaviors revolving around physical symptoms. Even when medical professionals assured no or low risk associated with somatic symptoms, individuals still experience excessive distress. Their lives may become centered around seeking medical attention, leading to frustration for both themselves and their families. When family members find it difficult to continue accommodating such behavior, patients may spiral into depressive states. The prevalence of somatic disorder is significant, comprising approximately 20% of initial consultations in general practices in the UK. Differential diagnosis is crucial, distinguishing somatization disorder from genuine medical conditions, hypochondriasis (distinguished by firmly held but unfounded illness beliefs), panic disorder, generalized anxiety disorder, and depression.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_AGRO_PHOBIA</LocID>
        <Text>Agoraphobia</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_NEW_PSY_AGRO_PHOBIA_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Agoraphobia is a condition characterized by an intense fear of specific places or situations. Individuals with agoraphobia typically experience fear in situations where escape might be difficult or help unavailable, such as in crowded places like conference halls or theaters, when using public transportation like buses, subways, or airplanes, and when being alone outside or even at home.</Text>
</GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      </LocalizedStrings>
  </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
