<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<Database>
  <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_NEW_PSYCHIATRY_PATCH">
    <LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
    <Contributors>
      <Name>banishee</Name>
    </Contributors>
    <LocalizedStrings>
    
     <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SNRIS_VENLAFAXINE</LocID>
        <Text>Venlafaxine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_SNRIS_VENLAFAXINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Venlafaxine, classified as a bicyclic phenylethylamine compound, differs structurally from other antidepressants and anxiolytics. It is a serotonin and norepinephrine reuptake inhibitor (SNRI) used to treat major depressive disorder, generalized anxiety disorder, social anxiety disorder, and panic attacks. Venlafaxine's safety and tolerability are similar to those of SSRIs, though it commonly causes nausea, more frequently than SSRIs, and also has sexual dysfunction as a side effect. Venlafaxine is one of the most commonly reported antidepressants associated with discontinuation syndrome. Additionally, it is used in the preventive treatment of migraines.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEMENTIA_MEDICINE_MEMANTINE</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Memantine</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEMENTIA_MEDICINE_MEMANTINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Memantine, marketed under the brand name Ebixa, is a non-competitive NMDA receptor antagonist. It is used for the treatment of moderate to severe Alzheimer's disease-related dementia, where it may offer efficacy in managing symptoms.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_SLEEPING_DRUGS_ZS_ZOLPIDEM</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Zolpidem</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_SLEEPING_DRUGS_ZS_ZOLPIDEM_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Zolpidem, marketed under the brand name Ambien, is an imidazopyridine class non-benzodiazepine sedative-hypnotic drug. It is a short-acting hypnotic agent with potent sedative effects, making it particularly effective for patients with difficulty falling asleep. Zolpidem significantly reduces sleep onset latency in individuals with insomnia. It works by selectively agonizing the ω-1 subtype of GABA_A receptors at the benzodiazepine (BZ) site, increasing chloride ion influx and enhancing the inhibitory effects of GABA.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_SLEEPING_DRUGS_ZS_ZALEPLON</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Zaleplon</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_SLEEPING_DRUGS_ZS_ZALEPLON_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Zaleplon is a non-benzodiazepine sedative-hypnotic drug that selectively agonizes the ω-1 subtype of GABA_A receptors at the benzodiazepine (BZ) site, leading to an increase in chloride ion influx and potentiation of GABA's inhibitory effects. It has a rapid onset of action and is quickly absorbed when taken orally, effectively reducing sleep onset latency. However, due to its short duration of action, zaleplon does not significantly increase total sleep time or reduce the number of awakenings throughout the night. It is primarily used for the short-term treatment of insomnia characterized by difficulty falling asleep.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_CARBAMAZEPINE</LocID>
        <Text>Carbamazepine</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NMC_CARBAMAZEPINE_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Carbamazepine is an anticonvulsant and mood stabilizer. In neurology, it is the first-line treatment for partial seizures, with superior efficacy for complex partial seizures compared to other antiepileptic drugs. It is also effective in treating secondary generalized tonic-clonic seizures but may exacerbate absence and myoclonic seizures. In psychiatry, carbamazepine is used for the treatment of acute manic episodes in bipolar disorder, particularly in patients who are unresponsive to lithium, or those experiencing rapid cycling or mixed episodes. Additionally, carbamazepine is employed in the management of certain types of neuropathic pain. It is important to note that carbamazepine is an inducer of various drug-metabolizing enzymes, which can lead to increased metabolism of concomitant medications, thereby reducing their plasma concentrations and potentially diminishing their therapeutic effects.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
		<GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_TCM_BAILEMIAN_CAPSULES</LocID>
        <Text>Bai Lemin capsules</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>TRT_NEW_PSY_ANTIDEPRESSSANT_DRUGS_TCM_BAILEMIAN_CAPSULES_DESC</LocID>
        <Text>Bai Lemin Capsules are a traditional Chinese medicine that has gained attention for its potential sleep-promoting effects based on clinical observations. The formulation includes ingredients such as Lily Bulb (Bai He), Eleuthero (Ciwujia), Fleeceflower Caulis (Shouwu Teng), Albizia Flower (Hehuan Hua), Mother-of-Pearl (Zhenzhumu), Gypsum (Shigao), Ziziphus Seed (Suanzaoren), Poria (Fuling), Polygala Root (Yuanzhi), Scrophularia Root (Xuanshen), Rehmannia Root (Dihuang), Ophiopogon Root (Maidong), Schisandra (Wuweizi), Juncus Pith (Dengxincao), and Salvia Root (Danshen). The capsules are believed to nourish Yin, clear heat, calm the mind, and are indicated for insomnia of the Yin deficiency with internal heat type. </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
      <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>TRT_NMC_AMITRIPTYLINE</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Amitriptyline</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>TRT_NMC_AMITRIPTYLINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Amitriptyline is a class of tricyclic antidepressants (TCAs) that can inhibit the reuptake of monoamine neurotransmitters and have strong sedative and anticholinergic effects. In the field of psychiatry, the tricyclic antidepressants to which amitriptyline belongs are now rarely used, but it has been found in clinical practice that amitriptyline is more effective in treating physical symptoms; In other specialized fields, amitriptyline is often used for the prevention and treatment of migraine and neuropathic pain, as well as for functional disorders such as irritable bowel syndrome and cardiac neurosis. In addition, the SNRI antidepressant drug duloxetine has been found to have good therapeutic effects on various physical discomforts and chronic pain.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
     
      </LocalizedStrings>
  </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
