<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<Database>
  <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_MOD_HEMATOLOGY_TREATMENTS">
    <LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
    <LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
    <Contributors>
      <Name>WDZRMPCBIT</Name>
    </Contributors>
    <LocalizedStrings>
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_CLADRIBINE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Cladribine IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_CLADRIBINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Cladribine is a purine analogue whose antineoplastic activity is related to the activity of deoxycytidine kinase and deoxynucleotide kinase. It is indicated for hairy cell leukemia.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ASPIRIN</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Aspirin</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ASPIRIN_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Aspirin, also known as acetylsalicylic acid, is an old and classic nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug (NSAID) with antipyretic, analgesic, anti-inflammatory, and antirheumatic effects. It is now commonly used as an antiplatelet agent to inhibit platelet aggregation.\n\nRequired Departments: Hematology, Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ECULIZUMAB</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Eculizumab IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ECULIZUMAB_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Eculizumab binds specifically and with high affinity to the complement protein C5, thereby inhibiting its cleavage into C5a and C5b and preventing the formation of the terminal complement complex C5b-9. It is indicated for the treatment of paroxysmal nocturnal hemoglobinuria (PNH).\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ZEBUTINIB</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Zanubrutinib Capsules</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ZEBUTINIB_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Zanubrutinib, trade name Brukinsa, is a selective Bruton's tyrosine kinase (BTK) inhibitor developed by BeiGene. It is a small-molecule targeted therapy drug indicated for adult mantle cell lymphoma (MCL), chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL), and Waldenström's macroglobulinemia (WM).\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_RUXOLITNIB</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Ruxolitinib</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_RUXOLITNIB_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Ruxolitinib, trade name Jakafi, is a selective inhibitor of Janus kinase 1 (JAK1) and Janus kinase 2 (JAK2). These kinases mediate the signaling of a number of important cytokines and growth factors involved in hematopoiesis and immune function. The drug is indicated for the treatment of splenomegaly and other symptoms associated with primary myelofibrosis.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_BENDAMUSTINE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Bendamustine IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_BENDAMUSTINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Bendamustine is a bifunctional nitrogen mustard derivative containing a purine-like benzimidazole ring. Nitrogen mustards and their derivatives can form electrophilic alkyl groups that form covalent bonds with electron-rich nucleophilic groups, causing interstrand DNA cross-links, which can lead to cell death through multiple pathways. Bendamustine is active against both quiescent and dividing cells, although its exact mechanism is not fully understood. Compared to chlorambucil, it can effectively improve the overall response rate and progression-free survival in the treatment of chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL).\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_CYCLOPHOSPHAMIDE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Cyclophosphamide IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_CYCLOPHOSPHAMIDE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Cyclophosphamide, brand name Cytoxan, is a cytotoxic agent of the alkylating class and chemically belongs to the nitrogen mustard group. It is a cell-cycle non-specific drug with a broad antineoplastic spectrum. It is inactive in vitro and is activated in the body by hepatic microsomal cytochrome P450, which cleaves the ring to form aldophosphamide. This is then broken down within tumor cells to release phosphamide mustard, which exerts its effect. It is highly effective against malignant lymphoma and also has some efficacy against multiple myeloma, acute lymphocytic leukemia, lung cancer, ovarian cancer, neuroblastoma, etc. Common adverse reactions include myelosuppression, nausea, vomiting, and alopecia. It is also used as a second-line therapy for the prevention of relapse in neuromyelitis optica spectrum disorder (NMOSD).\n\nRequired Departments: Hematology, Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_RITUXIMAB</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Rituximab IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_RITUXIMAB_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Rituximab, brand name Rituxan, is a chimeric murine/human monoclonal antibody that specifically binds to the transmembrane antigen CD20. The CD20 antigen is located on the surface of pre-B and mature B lymphocytes. After binding to the CD20 antigen on B cells, rituximab triggers an immune response that mediates B-cell lysis. It is indicated for non-Hodgkin's lymphoma and chronic lymphocytic leukemia. Rituximab is also used for the prevention of relapse in neuromyelitis optica spectrum disorder (NMOSD).\n\nRequired Departments: Hematology, Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_INTERFERON_ALPHA</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Intramuscular Interferon</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_INTERFERON_ALPHA_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Interferon is a class of naturally occurring cytokines with broad-spectrum antiviral, antitumor, and immunomodulatory functions. It binds to cell surface receptors, inducing cells to produce various antiviral proteins, thereby inhibiting viral replication. By modulating immune function, it can enhance the specific cytotoxic effects of macrophages and lymphocytes on target cells. It can also enhance natural killer (NK) cell activity and inhibit tumor cell growth. This drug is indicated for the treatment of viral diseases and certain malignancies. Interferon-alpha is relatively inexpensive and was a main choice for treating chronic myeloid leukemia (CML) before the advent of molecular targeted drugs, with complete remission rates up to 13% and 10-year survival rates of 70% in responders. Prophylactic use of acetaminophen can reduce its flu-like symptoms. Interferon is now also used in the treatment of myeloproliferative neoplasms.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_NILOTINIB</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Nilotinib</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_NILOTINIB_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Nilotinib, a second-generation tyrosine kinase inhibitor (TKI) (the first-generation TKI is imatinib, i.e., Gleevec), binds to and stabilizes the inactive conformation of the ABL protein kinase domain. It is an expensive molecularly targeted drug used for the treatment of chronic myeloid leukemia (CML).\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ATRA</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Tretinoin Tablets</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ATRA_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Tretinoin, also known as all-trans retinoic acid (ATRA), is used topically in dermatology for acne vulgaris. It can regulate and degrade the promyelocytic leukemia-retinoic acid receptor alpha (PML-RARα) fusion protein, which plays a key role in acute promyelocytic leukemia (APL). This restarts the gene regulatory network for myeloid cell differentiation, inducing leukemia cells to differentiate, mature, and subsequently undergo apoptosis. Therefore, in hematology, tretinoin is indicated for acute promyelocytic leukemia (APL, M3).\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ATO</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Arsenic Trioxide IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ATO_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Arsenic trioxide, also known as arsenous acid, selectively induces apoptosis in leukemia cells by degrading the PML domain of the PML-RARα fusion protein and downregulating BCL-2 gene expression. Arsenous acid is primarily used to treat acute promyelocytic leukemia (APL, M3), and it is now internationally recognized as a first-line drug for this disease. It generally does not cause side effects such as bleeding or myelosuppression. Through slow, long-term injection, it can maintain plasma concentrations that promote apoptosis without causing toxicity to vital organs, greatly improving its clinical safety. Due to its excellent efficacy, APL has become the first type of acute myeloid leukemia that can be largely cured.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_BLEOMYCIN</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Intramuscular Bleomycin</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_BLEOMYCIN_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Bleomycin is a chemotherapy drug. Its iron complex intercalates into DNA, causing single- and double-strand breaks. It is indicated for squamous cell carcinomas of the head and neck, esophagus, skin, cervix, vagina, vulva, and penis, as well as for Hodgkin's disease, malignant lymphomas, testicular cancer, and malignant pleural effusions.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>    
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DACARBAZINE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Dacarbazine IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DACARBAZINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Dacarbazine is a precursor in purine biosynthesis and interferes with it. After entering the body, it is demethylated by liver microsomes to form a monomethyl compound with direct cytotoxic effects. It primarily acts on the G2 phase, inhibiting the synthesis of purine, RNA, and protein, and also affects DNA synthesis. It is indicated for the treatment of melanoma and is also used for soft tissue sarcomas and malignant lymphomas.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_FUROSEMIDE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Furosemide</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_FUROSEMIDE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Furosemide, also known as Lasix, is a loop diuretic that promotes the excretion of water and electrolytes. It also has vasodilatory effects. It is indicated for edematous diseases, hypertension, prevention of acute renal failure, hyperkalemia, hypercalcemia, dilutional hyponatremia, syndrome of inappropriate antidiuretic hormone secretion (SIADH), and various types of acute drug poisoning.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DISODIUM_PAMIDRONATE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Pamidronate Disodium IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DISODIUM_PAMIDRONATE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Pamidronate disodium is a bisphosphonate drug. In vitro and in vivo studies have shown that it strongly inhibits hydroxyapatite and osteoclast activity, exerting a significant inhibitory effect on bone resorption. The drug has an analgesic effect on pain caused by osteolytic bone metastases from cancer and can also be used to treat cancer-related hypercalcemia.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ADRIAMYCIN</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Doxorubicin IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ADRIAMYCIN_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Doxorubicin, also known as Adriamycin, is an antimitotic cytotoxic drug. It can successfully induce remission in a variety of malignant tumors, including acute leukemias, lymphomas, soft tissue and bone sarcomas, pediatric malignancies, and adult solid tumors, especially breast and lung cancers.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_BORTEZOMIB</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Bortezomib IV Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_BORTEZOMIB_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Bortezomib is a reversible inhibitor of the chymotrypsin-like activity of the 26S proteasome in mammalian cells. In vitro studies have shown it to be cytotoxic to a variety of cancer cell types. In vivo preclinical tumor models have demonstrated its ability to delay tumor growth, including in multiple myeloma. Bortezomib is indicated for multiple myeloma and mantle cell lymphoma.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_VINCRISTINE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Vincristine IV Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_VINCRISTINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Vincristine is an active compound extracted from the Madagascar periwinkle. Its antitumor target is tubulin; it primarily inhibits tubulin polymerization, affecting the formation of the mitotic spindle and causing cell cycle arrest in metaphase. It also interferes with protein metabolism and inhibits RNA polymerase activity. It is used to treat acute leukemia, Hodgkin's disease, and malignant lymphoma, and also for breast cancer, bronchopulmonary carcinoma, soft tissue sarcomas, and neuroblastoma. Vincristine has nervous system toxicity and is the most likely (among vinca alkaloids) to cause peripheral neuropathy.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_L-ASPARAGINASE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>L-Asparaginase IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_L-ASPARAGINASE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>L-Asparaginase breaks down L-asparagine in the blood, leading to nutrient deprivation in tumor cells that require asparagine, thus exerting its antitumor effect. It is indicated for acute leukemia, the blast crisis phase of chronic leukemia, and malignant lymphoma.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DANAZOL</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Danazol</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DANAZOL_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Danazol is a gonadotropin inhibitor that can suppress the pituitary-ovarian axis. It can increase the body's erythropoietin levels and promote erythropoiesis.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_LENALIDOMIDE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Lenalidomide</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_LENALIDOMIDE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Lenalidomide is an analogue of thalidomide. It can inhibit the release of inflammatory factors such as tumor necrosis factor (TNF), inhibit angiogenesis, and promote the activation of T cells and NK cells, thereby exerting immunomodulatory, anti-angiogenic, and antitumor effects.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DECITABINE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Decitabine IV Infusion</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DECITABINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Decitabine is a demethylating agent. After phosphorylation, it is directly incorporated into DNA, inhibiting DNA methyltransferase. This leads to DNA hypomethylation and subsequent cell differentiation or apoptosis, which accounts for its antitumor effect. It is indicated for various types of myelodysplastic syndromes (MDS).\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_G-CSF</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Granulocyte Colony-Stimulating Factor (G-CSF) IV Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_G-CSF_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>This drug is a human granulocyte colony-stimulating factor (G-CSF) produced using recombinant DNA technology. Its biological activity is essentially identical to the natural product. It is one of the main factors regulating granulopoiesis in the bone marrow, selectively acting on granulopoietic progenitor cells to promote their proliferation and differentiation, and can also enhance the function of terminally differentiated granulocytic cells.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_METHYLPREDNISOLONE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Methylprednisolone IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_METHYLPREDNISOLONE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Methylprednisolone is a synthetic glucocorticoid. It is indicated for symptomatic anti-inflammatory and anti-allergic treatment.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_METACORTANDRACIN</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Prednisone Acetate Tablets</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_METACORTANDRACIN_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Prednisone is an adrenal corticosteroid drug with anti-inflammatory, anti-allergic, antirheumatic, and immunosuppressive effects. It is mainly used for allergic and autoimmune inflammatory diseases.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DEFEROXAMINE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Deferoxamine Mesylate IV Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DEFEROXAMINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Deferoxamine (DFO) is a chelating agent that forms complexes with trivalent iron and aluminum ions. It can be used to treat chronic iron overload, such as hemosiderosis caused by long-term, repeated blood transfusions. It is also indicated for the treatment of acute iron poisoning and chronic aluminum overload in patients with end-stage renal failure (on continuous dialysis).\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ALLOPURINOL</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Allopurinol</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ALLOPURINOL_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Allopurinol and its metabolite, oxypurinol, both inhibit xanthine oxidase. This prevents the metabolism of hypoxanthine and xanthine into uric acid, thereby reducing uric acid production. Allopurinol is mainly used for hyperuricemia, gout, uric acid kidney stones, and urate nephropathy. It can also be used to prevent hyperuricemia during the treatment of high-leukocyte acute leukemia.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_CYTARABINE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Cytarabine IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_CYTARABINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Cytarabine is an antimetabolite drug that inhibits the activity of DNA polymerase and can be incorporated into DNA, thus blocking DNA synthesis. It primarily acts on the S phase of the cell cycle, leading to cell death. Together with other cytotoxic agents, it is mainly used for the treatment of leukemia and lymphoma.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_IDARUBICIN</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Idarubicin IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_IDARUBICIN_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Idarubicin, also known as 4-demethoxydaunorubicin, is an antimitotic and cytotoxic agent. It is a DNA intercalator that acts on topoisomerase II, inhibiting nucleic acid synthesis. It has higher activity compared to daunorubicin and is mainly used for acute leukemia.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DAUNORUBICIN</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Daunorubicin IV Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DAUNORUBICIN_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Daunorubicin is an anthracycline antibiotic. Its antitumor action is the same as doxorubicin's. It selectively acts on purine nucleosides, inhibiting topoisomerase II activity, which affects tumor cell DNA transcription and replication. It is mainly used for acute lymphocytic or myeloid leukemia resistant to common antitumor drugs, but remission is short, so it requires combination with other drugs. Adverse reactions include cardiotoxicity, myelosuppression, and gastrointestinal reactions.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_HYDROXYUREA</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Hydroxyurea</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_HYDROXYUREA_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Hydroxyurea inhibits ribonucleotide reductase, preventing the conversion of cytidylate to deoxycytidylate, thereby inhibiting DNA synthesis. It selectively kills cells in the S phase and can be used as a synchronizing agent in chemotherapy to increase sensitivity to radiation and chemotherapy. Hydroxyurea has a significant therapeutic effect on chronic myeloid leukemia, provides temporary remission for melanoma, and can also be used as pre-treatment for acute lymphocytic leukemia.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_INTRATHECAL_INJECTION_DEXAMETHASONE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Intrathecal Dexamethasone Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_INTRATHECAL_INJECTION_DEXAMETHASONE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Dexamethasone is directly injected into the subarachnoid space via lumbar puncture, allowing it to diffuse throughout the cerebrospinal fluid and quickly reach effective drug concentrations. Dexamethasone is an adrenal corticosteroid with anti-inflammatory and immunosuppressive effects. It is primarily used for allergic and autoimmune inflammatory diseases, such as connective tissue diseases, acute leukemia, etc. It is also used in the combination therapy of malignant lymphomas. Intrathecal injection of dexamethasone + methotrexate and/or cytarabine is the recommended regimen for treating central nervous system leukemia.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DEXAMETHASONE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Dexamethasone IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DEXAMETHASONE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Dexamethasone is an adrenal corticosteroid with anti-inflammatory, anti-allergic, antirheumatic, and immunosuppressive effects. It is primarily used for allergic and autoimmune inflammatory diseases, such as connective tissue diseases, active rheumatic disease, rheumatoid arthritis, lupus erythematosus, severe bronchial asthma, severe dermatitis, ulcerative colitis, and acute leukemia. It is also used in the combination therapy of certain severe infections and moderate/malignant lymphomas.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_NMC_HYDROCORTISONE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Hydrocortisone IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_NMC_HYDROCORTISONE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Hydrocortisone is a glucocorticoid with anti-inflammatory, immunosuppressive, antitoxic, and anti-shock effects. It is suitable for rescuing critically ill patients, such as those with toxic infections, anaphylactic shock, severe adrenocortical insufficiency, connective tissue diseases, and severe allergic diseases like bronchial asthma. It can also be used to prevent and treat acute graft rejection. Hydrocortisone may also be used for short-term treatment of cerebral salt-wasting syndrome.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_INTRATHECAL_INJECTION_METHOTREXATE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Intrathecal Methotrexate Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_INTRATHECAL_INjection_METHOTREXATE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Methotrexate (MTX) is directly injected into the subarachnoid space via lumbar puncture, allowing it to diffuse throughout the cerebrospinal fluid and quickly reach effective drug concentrations. Methotrexate inhibits dihydrofolate reductase, thereby interfering with DNA synthesis, repair, and cell replication. It thus has broad-spectrum antitumor activity and can be used alone or in combination with other chemotherapy drugs. Additionally, it is used to treat severe, recalcitrant, disabling psoriasis that is unresponsive to conventional therapies. Intrathecal injection of dexamethasone + methotrexate and/or cytarabine is the recommended regimen for treating central nervous system leukemia.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_INTRATHECAL_INJECTION_CYTARABINE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Intrathecal Cytarabine Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_INTRATHECAL_INJECTION_CYTARABINE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Cytarabine is directly injected into the subarachnoid space via lumbar puncture, allowing it to diffuse throughout the cerebrospinal fluid and quickly reach effective drug concentrations. Cytarabine is an antimetabolite drug that inhibits the activity of DNA polymerase and can be incorporated into DNA, thus blocking DNA synthesis. It primarily acts on the S phase of the cell cycle, leading to cell death. Intrathecal injection of dexamethasone + methotrexate and/or cytarabine is the recommended regimen for treating central nervous system leukemia.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_TCM_ZAIZAOSHENGXUE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Zaizao Shengxue Tablets</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_TCM_ZAIZAOSHENGXUE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Zaizao Shengxue Tablets tonify the liver and kidney, and supplement qi and nourish the blood. It is used for blood deficiency and consumptive disease due to liver and kidney insufficiency and deficiency of both qi and blood, manifesting as palpitations, shortness of breath, dizziness, vertigo, fatigue, weakness in the loins and knees, pale complexion, and pale lips and nails, with or without bleeding. Also for aplastic anemia and iron deficiency anemia with the aforementioned syndromes.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_ANALGESICS</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Analgesics</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
	
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ETAMSYLATE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Etamsylate IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ETAMSYLATE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Etamsylate can increase capillary resistance, reduce capillary permeability, and enhance platelet aggregation and adhesion, promoting the release of clotting factors from platelets and shortening coagulation time to achieve hemostasis. It is a systemic hemostatic agent. It is suitable for preventing and treating bleeding before and after various surgeries, and can also be used for bleeding caused by platelet dysfunction or increased vascular fragility, as well as for hematemesis, hematuria, etc.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_AMINOMETHYLBENZOIC_ACID</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Aminomethylbenzoic Acid IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_AMINOMETHYLBENZOIC_ACID_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Aminomethylbenzoic acid is a procoagulant drug. Its structure allows it to competitively inhibit the adsorption of plasminogen onto the fibrin network, thus preventing its activation and protecting fibrin from being degraded by plasmin, thereby achieving hemostasis. It is indicated for bleeding caused by primary hyperfibrinolysis, including acute and chronic, localized, and systemic hyperfibrinolytic hemorrhage, the latter of which is common in cancer, leukemia, major obstetric surgery, and severe liver disease. Its antifibrinolytic activity is 5 times stronger than that of aminocaproic acid. The related drug, tranexamic acid, helps limit hematoma expansion in intracerebral hemorrhage and reduces early mortality, but its long-term benefit is uncertain, and its non-selective use is not recommended.\n\nRequired Departments: Hematology, Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_FERROUS_SULFATE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Ferrous Sulfate Tablets</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_FERROUS_SULFATE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Ferrous sulfate is an inexpensive inorganic iron salt. Oral administration can supplement iron and correct iron deficiency anemia. Common gastrointestinal side effects include nausea, vomiting, upper abdominal pain, and constipation. It is also often used for iron supplementation in the treatment of restless legs syndrome (RLS). The "Chinese Guidelines for the Diagnosis and Treatment of Restless Legs Syndrome" (2021) recommend: Ferrous sulfate 325 mg twice a day (containing 65 mg of elemental iron per dose), taken with 100 mg of vitamin C each time.\n\nRequired Departments: Hematology, Psychiatry.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_POLYSACCHARIDE_IRON_COMPLEX</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Polysaccharide Iron Complex</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_POLYSACCHARIDE_IRON_COMPLEX_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Polysaccharide iron complex is a low molecular weight polysaccharide-iron complex with an elemental iron content as high as 46%. As an organic iron supplement, it can rapidly increase blood iron levels and hemoglobin. Radioisotope tracer studies have confirmed that it is easily absorbed by the body with minimal gastrointestinal irritation or constipation.\n\nRequired Departments: Hematology, Psychiatry.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_TCM_SHENGXUEBAO_MIXTURE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Shengxuebao Mixture</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_TCM_SHENGXUEBAO_MIXTURE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Shengxuebao Mixture is composed of several herbs. It nourishes the liver and kidney, and benefits qi to generate blood. It is indicated for mental fatigue, weakness in the loins and knees, dizziness, tinnitus, palpitations, shortness of breath, insomnia, dry throat, and poor appetite due to liver and kidney insufficiency and deficiency of both qi and blood. Also for leukopenia caused by radiation or chemotherapy, and iron deficiency anemia with the aforementioned syndromes.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_MECOBALAMIN</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Mecobalamin</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_MECOBALAMIN_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Mecobalamin is an analogue of vitamin B12 (cyanocobalamin) and is a neurotrophic agent. It promotes the utilization of folic acid and nucleic acid metabolism, promotes axon regeneration, normalizes delayed synaptic transmission, and inhibits nerve degeneration. It is also used for megaloblastic anemia and peripheral neuropathy caused by vitamin B12 deficiency.\n\nRequired Departments: Hematology, Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_FOLIC_ACID</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Folic Acid</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_FOLIC_ACID_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Folic acid is a water-soluble B vitamin essential for cell growth and reproduction. It is indicated for folic acid deficiency from various causes and the resulting megaloblastic anemia, as a prophylactic supplement for pregnant and lactating women, and for folic acid deficiency caused by chronic hemolytic anemia.\n\nRequired Departments: Hematology, Neurology Medical Center.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ATG_ALG</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Anti-thymocyte Globulin (ATG) IV Drip</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ATG_ALG_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Anti-thymocyte globulin (porcine anti-human lymphocyte immunoglobulin) is a biological agent that inhibits the activation of lymphocytes after antigen recognition and specifically destroys lymphocytes. This drug is commonly used for the prevention and treatment of immune rejection in clinical organ transplantation, prevention of graft-versus-host disease in bone marrow transplantation, and treatment of severe aplastic anemia and pure red cell aplasia. It may also be applicable for autoimmune hemolytic anemia, primary immune thrombocytopenia, and other immune diseases.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_CYCLOSPORIN</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Cyclosporine</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_CYCLOSPORIN_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Cyclosporine, also known as Cyclosporin A (CsA), is an immunosuppressant that selectively arrests immunocompetent lymphocytes in the G0 or G1 phase of the cell cycle. Cyclosporine is mainly used for the prevention of rejection reactions in organ and bone marrow transplantation, and can also be used for aplastic anemia and autoimmune diseases. It does not affect the function of phagocytic cells and does not cause myelosuppression.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_TESTOSTERONE_PROPIONATE</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Intramuscular Testosterone Propionate</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_TESTOSTERONE_PROPIONATE_DESC</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Testosterone propionate is an androgenic drug. In high doses, it also has anti-estrogenic effects. It is indicated for primary or secondary male hypogonadism, delayed puberty in males, and palliative treatment of advanced breast cancer in postmenopausal women. It can also be used to increase erythropoietin levels in the body and promote hematopoiesis.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_RECOMBINANT_HUMAN_ERYTHROPOIETIN</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Recombinant Human Erythropoietin IV Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_RECOMBINANT_HUMAN_ERYTHROPOIETIN_DESC</LocID>                                         		
			<Text>Erythropoietin is an active glycoprotein secreted by the kidneys that acts on hematopoietic progenitor cells in the bone marrow to promote their proliferation and differentiation. Recombinant human erythropoietin (r-HuEPO) is synthesized using DNA recombinant technology, and its properties and biological activity are similar to the natural substance. Clinically, it is mostly used for anemia caused by various reasons, especially renal anemia. It is also effective for anemia caused by bone marrow hypofunction, cancer chemotherapy, etc.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_FVIII</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Recombinant Human Coagulation Factor VIII IV Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_FVIII_DESC</LocID>                                         		
			<Text>Recombinant human coagulation factor VIII is a recombinant DNA product. Its functional characteristics are comparable to those of endogenous factor VIII. Factor VIII is the specific coagulation factor that is deficient in patients with hemophilia A. Administration of this product can increase plasma levels of factor VIII and temporarily correct the coagulation defect in these patients.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_FIX</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Recombinant Human Coagulation Factor IX IV Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_FIX_DESC</LocID>                                         		
			<Text>Recombinant human coagulation factor IX can temporarily replace the coagulation factor IX required for effective clotting and can temporarily correct the coagulation defect in patients with hemophilia B. It is indicated for the control and prevention of bleeding in patients with hemophilia B.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DDAVP</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Desmopressin IV Injection</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DDAVP_DESC</LocID>                                         		
			<Text>Desmopressin, also known as DDAVP, is a derivative of vasopressin. It has a strong antidiuretic effect and a weak vasopressor effect. It can also promote the release of coagulation factor VIII clotting activity components from endothelial cells and also promote the release of von Willebrand factor, which enhances its activity. Therefore, it can be used to treat mild and some moderate cases of hemophilia A, as well as central diabetes insipidus or nocturnal enuresis.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DEXAMETHASONE_TABLETS</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Dexamethasone Acetate Tablets</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_DEXAMETHASONE_TABLETS_DESC</LocID>                                         		
			<Text>Dexamethasone is an adrenal corticosteroid drug. Its anti-inflammatory, anti-allergic, and anti-shock effects are more significant than prednisone's, while its effects on water and sodium retention are very mild. Its inhibitory effect on the pituitary-adrenal axis is stronger. It is primarily used for allergic and autoimmune inflammatory diseases, such as connective tissue diseases, rheumatoid arthritis, lupus erythematosus, severe dermatitis, acute leukemia, and malignant lymphoma. Long-term use of large doses can lead to diabetes, peptic ulcers, and Cushing's-like syndrome symptoms. Concurrent infections are also common.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ROMIPLOSTIM</LocID>                                          	
			<Text>Subcutaneous Romiplostim</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>TRT_HEM_ROMIPLOSTIM_DESC</LocID>                                         		
			<Text>Romiplostim binds to and activates the thrombopoietin (TPO) receptor, thereby promoting platelet production through a mechanism similar to endogenous TPO. Romiplostim is indicated for adult patients with chronic immune thrombocytopenia (ITP) who have had an insufficient response to other treatments. The drug has mild adverse reactions and is well-tolerated by patients.\n\nRequired Department: Hematology.</Text>  
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
    </LocalizedStrings>
  </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
