<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<Database>
  <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_HEMATOLOGY_DIAGNOSES">
    <LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
    <LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
    <Contributors>
      <Name>WDZRMPCBIT</Name>
    </Contributors>
    <LocalizedStrings>
  
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_063_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Essential thrombocythemia (ET), also known as primary thrombocythemia, is a clonal proliferative disorder of hematopoietic pluripotent stem cells. It is characterized by a significant and persistent increase in peripheral platelet count with abnormal function, and excessive proliferation of megakaryocytes in the bone marrow, without polycythemia or myelofibrosis with myeloid metaplasia. Clinically, it often presents with splenomegaly, bleeding, and thrombosis. This condition is relatively rare, more common in middle-aged and elderly individuals, and slightly more prevalent in females than males. The direct cause of ET is unclear but may be related to gene mutations, whose abnormal activation leads to excessive production of megakaryocytes. The onset is insidious, and manifestations are inconsistent. Mild cases may have no symptoms other than fatigue and are occasionally diagnosed upon finding thrombocytosis or splenomegaly. The disease is also often discovered when patients seek treatment for bleeding tendencies. Thrombosis and embolism caused by ET frequently occur in the splenic, hepatic, mesenteric veins, axillary artery, intracranial arteries, and lower limb arteries and veins, often causing corresponding symptoms. This is due to extremely high platelet counts and, in some patients, increased platelet adhesiveness, leading to arterial or venous thrombosis. Approximately 50% to 80% of patients may have splenomegaly, but it is mostly moderate and rarely severe. A few cases may transform into acute leukemia, presenting with clinical manifestations of leukemia. ET needs to be differentiated from secondary thrombocythemia caused by factors such as post-splenectomy state or acute blood loss. The treatment goal is to reduce the platelet count to prevent and control adverse events. First-line treatments include antiplatelet aggregation drugs and cytoreductive therapy, such as hydroxyurea and interferon-alpha. Plateletpheresis may be used in particularly necessary or emergency situations. Second-line treatments include radionuclide therapy and busulfan. Most cases progress slowly, and the disease course varies depending on the degree of thrombocytosis, with a median survival of 10 to 15 years or more.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
  
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_IDA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Iron deficiency anemia (IDA) is a type of nutritional anemia and the most common type of anemia in clinical practice. It is caused by an imbalance between the body's iron supply and demand due to various reasons. Iron is one of the most important trace elements in the human body, widely distributed in various tissues and involved in multiple metabolic processes. Iron is also a raw material for hemoglobin synthesis. The main causes of IDA include insufficient iron intake (e.g., picky eating in children or increased iron demand in pregnant or lactating women), iron absorption disorders (e.g., various digestive diseases), and excessive iron loss (e.g., gastrointestinal bleeding), as well as transport and utilization disorders. In addition to the manifestations of the primary cause of iron deficiency, anemic symptoms include pale skin and mucous membranes, fatigue, easy exhaustion, dizziness, headache, tinnitus, palpitations, shortness of breath, poor appetite, and increased heart rate. Tissue ischemia can also lead to neurological abnormalities, growth retardation in children, dry and brittle hair, dry skin, and thin, brittle nails. The blood picture of IDA shows microcytic hypochromic anemia. Serum ferritin is the WHO-recommended standard for diagnosing IDA in our country. Bone marrow aspirates and other laboratory tests also show corresponding changes. For IDA, emphasis should be on etiological diagnosis; actively identifying and treating the underlying cause is crucial for a cure. IDA should be differentiated from sideroblastic anemia, thalassemia, anemia of chronic disease, and atransferrinemia. In terms of iron supplementation therapy, therapeutic iron preparations are divided into two categories: inorganic and organic iron. Inorganic iron is represented by ferrous sulfate, while organic iron includes iron dextran, ferrous gluconate, and iron polysaccharide complexes. The side effects of inorganic iron are more pronounced than those of organic iron. Oral iron supplements should be the first choice for treatment. If oral iron cannot be tolerated or if changes in the normal anatomy of the gastrointestinal tract affect iron absorption, injectable iron can be used. The anemic symptoms of IDA can be improved by iron supplementation, but the prognosis of IDA mainly depends on whether the primary disease can be cured.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_MA</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Megaloblastic Anemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_MA_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Megaloblastic anemia (MA) is a disease primarily caused by impaired deoxyribonucleic acid (DNA) synthesis due to vitamin B12 and folate deficiency, which slows down the rate of DNA replication. It can also be caused by hereditary or acquired disorders of DNA synthesis. It is characterized by macrocytic anemia, imbalanced nuclear-cytoplasmic development in bone marrow hematopoietic cells, forming megaloblasts, giant granulocytes, and megakaryocytes, and ineffective hematopoiesis leading to pancytopenia in peripheral blood. In severe deficiency, impaired DNA synthesis also affects rapidly proliferating tissues, such as the gastrointestinal mucosal epithelial cells, which show megaloblastic changes and atrophy, leading to corresponding clinical symptoms. In vitamin B12 deficiency, the synthesis of myelin phospholipids is also affected, resulting in neurological symptoms. The disease has an insidious onset and slow progression. The severity of anemia depends on the speed of onset and severity of folate and vitamin B12 deficiency, as well as the patient's general condition. By the time of diagnosis, most patients have developed moderate to severe anemia. In addition to general anemic symptoms, some patients may have mild jaundice. Severe cases may also have reduced white blood cell and platelet counts, a tendency for infection and bleeding, and a few patients may have splenomegaly. The disease can also have gastrointestinal manifestations, as well as neurological and psychiatric symptoms associated with vitamin B12 deficiency. Biochemical tests may show reduced levels of blood folate and/or vitamin B12, and red blood cell folate content. Serum homocysteine and methylmalonic acid levels are also helpful in diagnosis. The disease should be differentiated from hematological malignancies, autoimmune red cell diseases, and non-hematopoietic system diseases. In terms of treatment, the first step should be to remove the inducing factors and treat the primary disease, while supplementing with folic acid or vitamin B12.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_MM</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Multiple Myeloma</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_MM_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Multiple myeloma (MM) is a malignant proliferative disease of plasma cells and the most common type of malignant plasma cell disorder. It is characterized by the malignant proliferation of monoclonal plasma cells in the bone marrow, which secrete large amounts of monoclonal immunoglobulin or its fragments (M protein), leading to damage to related target organs or tissues. Common clinical manifestations include bone lesions, anemia, renal impairment, hypercalcemia, and infections. It accounts for about 1% of all malignant tumors and 10% of hematological malignancies. The pathogenesis of MM is complex and multi-staged. In recent years, research on its pathogenesis has mainly focused on cytogenetic abnormalities, the role of cytokines, the interaction between the bone marrow microenvironment and MM cells, the development of MM bone disease, and epigenetics. It often has an insidious onset. The main clinical manifestations are hypercalcemia, renal impairment, anemia, and bone lesions (CRAB symptoms), as well as target organ damage such as infections and hyperviscosity syndrome. Bone pain is the most common early symptom, most frequently in the lumbosacral region. Anemia is another common initial symptom, and patients often have mucocutaneous bleeding. 30% to 50% of patients present with varying degrees and types of renal injury at diagnosis. Hypercalcemia and hyperuricemia may also occur. Patients often have varying degrees of humoral immune deficiency, accompanied by abnormal MM cell function, making them extremely susceptible to infections. Neuropathy can also be caused by various factors. The incidence of extramedullary disease is 39% to 19%, while the incidence of amyloidosis is 10% to 25%. The anemia caused by this disease is normocytic normochromic. Treatment for newly diagnosed patients should include systematic therapy such as induction, consolidation, and maintenance. Common induction regimens include VAD (the module uses this regimen: bortezomib, doxorubicin, and dexamethasone), VD, VTD, DTPACE, etc. Bisphosphonates should be used for bone disease. Hypercalcemia should be treated with aggressive hydration and diuresis. Renal insufficiency should also be managed with enhanced hydration, alkalinization, and diuresis to reduce uric acid formation and promote its excretion. Erythropoietin can be used for anemia. For patients with recurrent infections, intravenous immunoglobulin infusion can be considered. Peripheral neuropathy can be prevented with vitamins, cytoprotective agents, etc. Some studies have shown that acupuncture combined with neurotrophic drugs has a good effect on peripheral neuropathy. Currently, MM is still an incurable disease. The prognosis is related to host factors, tumor biology and tumor burden, and the type of treatment implemented.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_AA</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Aplastic Anemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_AA_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Aplastic anemia (AA) is a bone marrow failure syndrome caused by various etiologies and mechanisms. Its incidence in our country is about 0.74/100,000. Its main manifestations are pancytopenia, anemia, infection (often causing fever), and bleeding. Immunosuppressive therapy is effective. The disease can be divided into congenital and acquired types. Congenital AA mainly includes Fanconi anemia, dyskeratosis congenita, and Shwachman-Diamond syndrome. The cause of acquired aplastic anemia is unclear (possibly viral infection or chemical/physical factors), and its pathogenesis is complex (mainly including hematopoietic stem and progenitor cell defects, abnormal hematopoietic microenvironment, immune abnormalities, and genetic background factors). It refers to pancytopenia caused by primary bone marrow hypoplasia without fibrosis or abnormal infiltration. Based on the patient's blood counts, bone marrow findings, disease progression, and prognosis, the disease is divided into severe and non-severe types. Acquired aplastic anemia should be differentiated from hereditary and other bone marrow failure syndromes. In terms of treatment, the principle for severe AA should emphasize "fast diagnosis, strict isolation, early treatment, high dosage, and sufficient course." This includes treatment targeting the pathogenesis (i.e., bone marrow transplantation or combined immunosuppressive therapy) and supportive care (including correcting anemia, controlling bleeding, controlling infectious fever, iron chelation therapy, and liver protection). For non-severe patients, treatment with cyclosporine plus hematopoietic stimulants (androgens or hematopoietic growth factors) or cyclosporine alone may be chosen, depending on whether they are dependent on blood product transfusions. Strengthening labor and living environmental protection, improving personal protection awareness, reducing or eliminating exposure to various types of radiation, avoiding contact with toxic chemicals, especially benzene compounds, and trying to avoid drugs that may damage the bone marrow are the principles for preventing this disease. Its prognosis is related to the severity of the condition, age, and whether treatment is timely. One-third of severe patients still die from infection and bleeding.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_PRCA</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Pure Red Cell Aplasia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_PRCA_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Pure red cell aplasia (PRCA) is a group of disorders characterized by a selective failure of erythropoiesis in the bone marrow, leading to a reduction in peripheral reticulocytes and mature red blood cells, while white blood cells and platelets remain essentially normal. It can be classified as congenital or acquired. It is mainly caused by impaired generation of erythroid lineage cells due to various factors, such as viruses, thymoma, drugs, lymphoproliferative diseases, and autoimmune disorders, resulting in a decrease in the number of cells at all stages of erythropoiesis. Some patients are primary, with no clear cause found. It is generally believed that this disease is caused by B-lymphocyte and/or T-lymphocyte immune abnormalities. Clinically, anemic symptoms are common, and patients with long-term anemia are prone to developing anemic heart disease. Some patients have a concurrent thymoma, which is not easily detected by physical examination and is often found by chest X-ray or CT. Those with concurrent diseases often show manifestations of the primary disease. Laboratory tests may reveal normocytic normochromic anemia, reduced or absent reticulocytes, and normal white blood cell and platelet counts with a normal differential. Bone marrow is hypercellular, but the erythroid series is significantly reduced or absent, while other systems are largely normal. Some patients may have elevated gamma globulins, and the appearance of heterophile antibodies and autoantibodies. Serum iron and ferritin may also be increased, with elevated iron saturation and decreased iron utilization. In terms of treatment, patients with severe anemia need red blood cell transfusions, and their body iron load should be evaluated with attention to iron chelation therapy. To address the cause, suspicious drugs should be discontinued. For thymoma, the thymus should be removed as soon as possible. Patients with parvovirus B19 infection should receive timely antiviral treatment or high-dose intravenous immunoglobulin. Adrenocorticosteroids are the first-line treatment for this disease, with prednisone being commonly used. Cyclosporine is also a first-line drug. Although recombinant human erythropoietin and high-dose gamma globulin are effective second-line treatments, they are more expensive. There are few reports on the treatment of this disease with anti-human thymocyte globulin at home and abroad, so it should be chosen with caution. Allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation is the only curative method for congenital PRCA. The prognosis for patients with secondary PRCA depends on the primary disease; most respond to immunosuppressants and have a long survival.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_CML</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Chronic Myeloid Leukemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_CML_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Chronic myeloid leukemia (CML), also known as chronic myelogenous leukemia, is a malignant myeloproliferative neoplasm originating from an early pluripotent hematopoietic stem cell (an acquired malignant clonal disease of hematopoietic stem cells). The disease develops relatively slowly, mainly involving the myeloid lineage, with a significant increase in peripheral granulocytes and the presence of immature forms, and often an enlarged spleen. All patients have the characteristic Philadelphia chromosome in the affected cell lines (essentially a translocation of the C-ABL proto-oncogene from chromosome 9 to chromosome 22, where it joins with the breakpoint cluster region (BCR) at the breakpoint). The natural course of CML is divided into the chronic phase (CP), accelerated phase (AP), and blastic phase (BP), with the latter two collectively known as the advanced phase. This disease accounts for about 15% of adult leukemias. Patients in the chronic phase may have symptoms of hypermetabolism such as fatigue, low-grade fever, night sweats, and weight loss. Due to splenomegaly, they may feel a sense of fullness in the upper left abdomen, which is often a prominent sign. Patients in the accelerated phase often have fever, weakness, progressive weight loss, bone pain, and gradually develop anemia and bleeding, with a persistently or progressively enlarging spleen that is unresponsive to previously effective drugs. The terminal phase of the disease in most cases transforms into acute myeloid leukemia, and a minority transform into acute lymphoblastic leukemia or acute monocytic leukemia. Laboratory tests show a significantly elevated white blood cell count in the blood, and the bone marrow shows corresponding manifestations. Treatment for this disease should focus on the early chronic phase to prevent disease transformation and strive to achieve cytogenetic and molecular remission as soon as possible. Once the disease enters the advanced phase, the prognosis is poor. For hyperleukocytosis, hydroxyurea can be used emergently to lower the white blood cell count, along with appropriate hydration and uric acid-lowering treatment. Current international guidelines recommend molecularly targeted therapy, TKI (tyrosine kinase inhibitors), as a first-line treatment for newly diagnosed chronic phase patients. Commonly used drugs include imatinib (Gleevec, first-generation) and nilotinib (second-generation). Patients who cannot use TKI therapy may consider interferon, hydroxyurea, etc. After entering the advanced phase, the dose of TKI can be increased, and combined with chemotherapy to improve the induction remission rate. After remission, allo-HSCT (allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation) should be performed as soon as possible. Many factors affect the chronic phase and survival of patients with this disease. Various scoring systems can be used for monitoring.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_AML</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Acute Myeloid Leukemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_AML_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Leukemia is the most representative hematologic malignancy of the hematopoietic system, a malignant clonal disease originating from hematopoietic stem cells. Acute leukemia is poorly differentiated and progresses rapidly, with a natural course of only a few months. Acute leukemia can be divided into acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL) and acute myeloid leukemia (AML) based on the affected cell lineage. Leukemia is a relatively common hematologic malignancy worldwide. The etiology of human leukemia is complex and mainly related to biological (viral), physical, chemical, and genetic factors, as well as the progression of other blood diseases. The abnormal proliferation of leukemic cells severely inhibits bone marrow hematopoietic function, leading to reduced production of normal blood cells and a series of corresponding clinical manifestations, which are mostly non-specific. Most patients may present with fever in the early stages, ranging from high to low grade. The main cause of fever is related to the abnormal number and function of white blood cells in leukemia patients and the susceptibility to infection due to immunodeficiency. Nearly 40% of acute leukemia patients present with bleeding as an early manifestation. The vast majority of patients have varying degrees of anemia at the time of diagnosis, mostly severe, and it worsens progressively. Leukemic cell proliferation and infiltration can manifest as lymphadenopathy and splenomegaly, localized tenderness at the lower end of the sternum, bone pain when leukemic cells involve the periosteum, bone, and joints, and severe bone pain in cases of bone marrow necrosis. A few patients have leukemic cell infiltration into the eyes, oral cavity, and skin, causing corresponding symptoms. When leukemic cells involve the central nervous system and cause symptoms, it is called central nervous system leukemia. About 10% of patients have an anterior mediastinal (thymic) mass, and testicular infiltration, also known as testicular leukemia, can also occur. A complete blood count is the most basic test for diagnosing acute leukemia, with most patients showing an elevated WBC. Bone marrow aspiration smears and bone marrow biopsy sections are important examinations for diagnosing leukemia. In addition, cytochemical staining, immunological tests, cytogenetics, and molecular biology tests are also useful. General treatment for acute leukemia includes correction of blood cell abnormalities (pre-treatment with hydroxyurea can be given before chemotherapy for hyperleukocytic acute myeloid leukemia), prevention and control of infections, treatment of metabolic complications (allopurinol is used to prevent hyperuricemia), and nutritional support. Chemotherapy regimens for induction remission of acute myeloid leukemia mainly include IA, DA, HA, and MA (the module uses IA, i.e., idarubicin and cytarabine). Acute leukemia is treatable, but without treatment, the median survival is only about three months, with a risk of death at any time.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_APL</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Acute Promyelocytic Leukemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_APL_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Leukemia is the most representative hematologic malignancy of the hematopoietic system, a malignant clonal disease originating from hematopoietic stem cells. Acute leukemia is poorly differentiated and progresses rapidly, with a natural course of only a few months. Acute leukemia can be divided into acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL) and acute myeloid leukemia (AML) based on the affected cell lineage. Leukemia is a relatively common hematologic malignancy worldwide. The etiology of human leukemia is complex and mainly related to biological (viral), physical, chemical, and genetic factors, as well as the progression of other blood diseases. The abnormal proliferation of leukemic cells severely inhibits bone marrow hematopoietic function, leading to reduced production of normal blood cells and a series of corresponding clinical manifestations, which are mostly non-specific. Most patients may present with fever in the early stages, ranging from high to low grade. The main cause of fever is related to the abnormal number and function of white blood cells in leukemia patients and the susceptibility to infection due to immunodeficiency. Nearly 40% of acute leukemia patients present with bleeding as an early manifestation. The vast majority of patients have varying degrees of anemia at the time of diagnosis, mostly severe, and it worsens progressively. Leukemic cell proliferation and infiltration can manifest as lymphadenopathy and splenomegaly, localized tenderness at the lower end of the sternum, bone pain when leukemic cells involve the periosteum, bone, and joints, and severe bone pain in cases of bone marrow necrosis. A few patients have leukemic cell infiltration into the eyes, oral cavity, and skin, causing corresponding symptoms. When leukemic cells involve the central nervous system and cause symptoms, it is called central nervous system leukemia. About 10% of patients have an anterior mediastinal (thymic) mass, and testicular infiltration, also known as testicular leukemia, can also occur. A complete blood count is the most basic test for diagnosing acute leukemia, with most patients showing an elevated WBC. Bone marrow aspiration smears and bone marrow biopsy sections are important examinations for diagnosing leukemia. In addition, cytochemical staining, immunological tests, cytogenetics, and molecular biology tests are also useful. General treatment for acute leukemia includes correction of blood cell abnormalities (pre-treatment with hydroxyurea can be given before chemotherapy for hyperleukocytic acute myeloid leukemia), prevention and control of infections, treatment of metabolic complications (allopurinol is used to prevent hyperuricemia), and nutritional support. A dual-induction regimen of all-trans retinoic acid (ATRA) and arsenic trioxide (ATO) is commonly used for acute promyelocytic leukemia. Due to the excellent efficacy of arsenic trioxide, acute promyelocytic leukemia has become the first type of acute myeloid leukemia that can be largely cured. Acute leukemia is treatable, but without treatment, the median survival is only about three months, with a risk of death at any time.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_CLL</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Chronic Lymphocytic Leukemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_CLL_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL) and small lymphocytic lymphoma (SLL) are different manifestations of the same disease, a clonal proliferative disorder of mature B-cells with a specific immunophenotype, characterized by the progressive accumulation of monoclonal, mature CD5+ B-lymphocytes in the peripheral blood, bone marrow, liver, spleen, and lymph nodes. It is the most common adult leukemia in Western countries, accounting for 30% of all leukemias. Its exact etiology and pathogenesis are not well understood, and ionizing radiation, chemical carcinogens, pesticides, and viral infections are not related to the development of the disease. Western data show that old age, male sex, Caucasian race, a family history of other chronic lymphoproliferative diseases, and monoclonal B-cell lymphocytosis are risk factors for the disease. In addition, chromosomal abnormalities, gene mutations, clonal evolution, epigenetic changes, and the microenvironment also play important roles in its development. The onset of the disease is slow, and up to 70-80% of patients are asymptomatic in the early stages, often being diagnosed for the first time due to lymphadenopathy, hepatosplenomegaly, or abnormal blood counts found during a physical examination. Patients often have no obvious symptoms at presentation but may have fever, night sweats, and weight loss. Herpes simplex lesions may appear on the nose, lips, or genitals. 30-50% of patients have skin lesions, which are caused by allergic reactions to insect bites or leukemic cell infiltration. As the disease progresses, especially when treatment is ineffective, recurrent infections may be seen. In the late stages, due to impaired bone marrow hematopoietic function, anemia and thrombocytopenia occur. Patients with this disease often have autoimmune dysfunction and may develop autoimmune diseases, with an incidence of about 10%-25%. A small number of patients may have paraneoplastic syndromes and may develop secondary tumors. Laboratory tests show corresponding changes in the blood count. Peripheral blood smears are often used. The diagnosis of this disease does not require bone marrow aspiration or biopsy. Flow cytometry immunophenotyping is of great significance for the diagnosis. Cytogenetic and molecular biology tests are also available. Whether for initial, relapsed, or refractory CLL patients, treatment should only be initiated when treatment indications are met, such as progressive bone marrow failure, massive splenomegaly, or progressive lymphocytosis. Current treatment options for this disease mainly include immunochemotherapy, targeted drug therapy, and cell therapy. Immunochemotherapy refers to monoclonal antibodies combined with chemotherapy and is the traditional regimen for this disease. Bendamustine combined with rituximab, or fludarabine combined with cyclophosphamide are commonly used. The application of effective small molecule targeted therapies is an important advancement in the treatment of this disease. BTK inhibitors, such as ibrutinib or zanubrutinib, are commonly used. Available data still show that allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation is the only curative method for this disease.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_AAL</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_AAL_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Leukemia is the most representative hematologic malignancy of the hematopoietic system, a malignant clonal disease originating from hematopoietic stem cells. Acute leukemia is poorly differentiated and progresses rapidly, with a natural course of only a few months. Acute leukemia can be divided into acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL) and acute myeloid leukemia (AML) based on the affected cell lineage. Leukemia is a relatively common hematologic malignancy worldwide. The etiology of human leukemia is complex and mainly related to biological (viral), physical, chemical, and genetic factors, as well as the progression of other blood diseases. The abnormal proliferation of leukemic cells severely inhibits bone marrow hematopoietic function, leading to reduced production of normal blood cells and a series of corresponding clinical manifestations, which are mostly non-specific. Most patients may present with fever in the early stages, ranging from high to low grade. The main cause of fever is related to the abnormal number and function of white blood cells in leukemia patients and the susceptibility to infection due to immunodeficiency. Nearly 40% of acute leukemia patients present with bleeding as an early manifestation. The vast majority of patients have varying degrees of anemia at the time of diagnosis, mostly severe, and it worsens progressively. Leukemic cell proliferation and infiltration can manifest as lymphadenopathy and splenomegaly, localized tenderness at the lower end of the sternum, bone pain when leukemic cells involve the periosteum, bone, and joints, and severe bone pain in cases of bone marrow necrosis. A few patients have leukemic cell infiltration into the eyes, oral cavity, and skin, causing corresponding symptoms. When leukemic cells involve the central nervous system and cause symptoms, it is called central nervous system leukemia. About 10% of patients have an anterior mediastinal (thymic) mass, and testicular infiltration, also known as testicular leukemia, can also occur. A complete blood count is the most basic test for diagnosing acute leukemia, with most patients showing an elevated WBC. Bone marrow aspiration smears and bone marrow biopsy sections are important methods for understanding the morphological changes of bone marrow cells and the overall structure and distribution of hematopoietic tissue, and are one of the important examinations for diagnosing leukemia. In addition, cytochemical staining, immunological tests, cytogenetics, and molecular biology tests are also useful. Acute leukemia should be differentiated from leukemoid reaction, myelodysplastic syndrome, infectious mononucleosis, and aplastic anemia. General treatment for acute leukemia includes correction of blood cell abnormalities (pre-treatment with dexamethasone can be given before chemotherapy for hyperleukocytic acute lymphoblastic leukemia), prevention and control of infections, treatment of metabolic complications (allopurinol is used to prevent hyperuricemia), and nutritional support. Chemotherapy regimens for induction remission of acute lymphoblastic leukemia mainly include VP, DVLP, and hyper-CVAD (the module uses DVLP, i.e., daunorubicin, vincristine, L-asparaginase, and prednisone). Acute leukemia is treatable, but without treatment, the median survival is only about three months, with a risk of death at any time.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_THL</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Thalassemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_THL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Thalassemia, also known as Mediterranean anemia, is a group of inherited hemolytic diseases caused by the reduced or absent synthesis of one or more globin chains due to abnormalities in one or more globin genes, leading to an imbalance in the ratio of globin chains. It can be classified into alpha, beta, and other types of thalassemia based on the affected globin chain, with the first two being the most common. This disease is an autosomal incompletely dominant inherited disorder with a worldwide distribution, more common in Southeast Asia and the Mediterranean region. The southwest and southern regions of our country are high-prevalence areas. Thalassemia is a genetic disease, and a clinical diagnosis is not difficult based on family history, clinical manifestations, hemolytic screening tests, and specific diagnostic tests for the disease (such as target cells on blood smear, decreased osmotic fragility of red blood cells, abnormal hemoglobin electrophoresis, etc.). Depending on the type and severity of the disease, treatment is mainly symptomatic, including red blood cell transfusions, prevention of secondary hemochromatosis, and splenectomy. Factors that induce hemolysis should be actively prevented and treated. Although patients with mild forms do not require treatment, marriage between carriers may produce offspring with severe anemia. Therefore, prenatal genetic diagnosis and genetic counseling can effectively prevent the birth of fetuses with severe thalassemia and are of great significance in reducing the birth rate of severely affected children.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HLA</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Autoimmune Hemolytic Anemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HLA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Autoimmune hemolytic anemia (AIHA) is a hemolytic anemia caused by the accelerated destruction of red blood cells due to the production of autoantibodies against them, as a result of abnormal immune regulation in the body, which exceeds the compensatory capacity of the bone marrow. The main types of anti-erythrocyte antibodies that cause AIHA in humans are IgG and IgM. Based on the optimal temperature at which the antibodies act on red blood cells, they are divided into warm antibody type and cold antibody type, with the former accounting for about 70%. Occasionally, a mixed type with both is seen. It is classified as primary or secondary depending on whether the cause is clear. The warm antibody type is described below. Warm antibody AIHA can be secondary to lymphoproliferative diseases, autoimmune diseases, microbial infections, drugs, and other conditions. Its main pathogenesis is due to immune dysregulation, where the body produces autoantibodies against red blood cell membrane antigens. Red blood cells coated with autoantibodies are mainly destroyed in the mononuclear phagocyte system, resulting in extravascular hemolysis. The clinical manifestation of this disease is chronic extravascular hemolysis. It is more common in adult females. Jaundice, mild to moderate splenomegaly (in more than 1/2 of cases), and hepatomegaly (in more than 1/3 of cases) can be seen. In terms of examination, a complete blood count can confirm the presence of anemia. Various hemolytic screening tests can determine the presence and site of hemolysis. The disease can be definitively diagnosed through specific tests for red blood cell autoantibodies. In addition to etiological treatment, supportive care should aim to avoid or reduce blood transfusions. However, if transfusion criteria are met, red blood cells can be transfused immediately, but strict cross-matching, avoiding blood group antigens corresponding to the patient's autoantibodies, administering sufficient anti-allergic drugs before transfusion, slow transfusion speed, and close observation are necessary. Other measures include prophylactic anticoagulant therapy and supplementation of hematopoietic raw materials. For controlling hemolysis, adrenocorticosteroids are commonly used as first-line treatment, with an effectiveness rate of over 80%. Second-line treatments include splenectomy, rituximab, other immunosuppressants, high-dose intravenous immunoglobulin, danazol, and plasma exchange. The vast majority of patients can return to normal blood counts after active treatment but require maintenance therapy for several months to several years. The prognosis of secondary cases largely depends on the severity of the primary underlying disease.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_MDS</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Myelodysplastic Syndrome</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_MDS_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Myelodysplastic syndrome (MDS) is a group of heterogeneous myeloid clonal diseases originating from hematopoietic stem cells, characterized by abnormal differentiation and maturation of one or more cell lineages (granulocytic, erythroid, and megakaryocytic). It manifests as ineffective hematopoiesis, refractory cytopenias, hematopoietic failure, and even a high risk of transformation to acute myeloid leukemia. The disease is common in the elderly, with the annual incidence increasing with age, and is slightly more common in males than females. Its etiology and pathogenesis mainly include clonal dysplastic and ineffective hematopoiesis caused by hematopoietic stem cell abnormalities, genetic polymorphisms leading to individual susceptibility differences, primary and secondary factors, chromosomal abnormalities and gene mutations, and changes in the bone marrow microenvironment. The French-American-British (FAB) Cooperative Group and the World Health Organization have successively proposed classification schemes for the disease. The clinical manifestations are mainly caused by refractory cytopenias and are related to the affected cell lineage and the degree of reduction, with relative differences in clinical manifestations between lineages. Anemic symptoms may be present. Neutropenia and functional decline make MDS patients susceptible to infection. Thrombocytopenia can lead to bleeding. Disease progression may lead to leukemia-related symptoms. Laboratory and ancillary tests for this disease mainly include blood and bone marrow analysis, bone marrow pathology, in vitro colony culture of hematopoietic progenitor cells, cytogenetics, flow cytometry, and molecular genetics. The disease should be differentiated from congenital or hereditary blood diseases, other diseases affecting hematopoietic stem cells, vitamin B12 or folate deficiency, exposure to cytotoxic substances, cytokine therapy, or contact with hematotoxic chemicals or biological agents, anemia of chronic disease or viral infection, autoimmune cytopenias, hypothyroidism/hyperthyroidism, heavy metal poisoning, excessive alcohol consumption, and copper deficiency. The natural course and prognosis of this disease are highly variable, and individualized treatment is appropriate. Supportive care includes red blood cell transfusions for patients with severe anemia, or platelet transfusions for those with bleeding risk factors, with attention to iron chelation therapy. Hematopoietic stimulants such as androgens or various hematopoietic cell growth factors can be used. The choice of immunosuppressive and immunomodulatory therapy, as well as demethylating agents, depends on the subtype. Allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation is currently the only curative method for this disease. The clinical course of MDS has three developmental trends: long-term stable condition, initial stability followed by sudden disease progression, and gradual increase of bone marrow blasts with a slow but irreversible progression until leukemia develops.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HPL</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Hemophilia A</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HPL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Hemophilia is a group of inherited bleeding disorders caused by the reduction, absence, or dysfunction of coagulation factors, inherited in an X-linked recessive manner. Hemophilia A, also known as classic hemophilia or coagulation factor VIII:C deficiency, accounts for about 80%-85% of hemophilia cases. It is characterized by a positive family history, onset in childhood, uncontrollable bleeding after spontaneous or minor trauma, joint bleeding, and deep muscle hematomas. Patients have varying degrees of reduced plasma factor VIII levels. Clinically, bleeding manifestations can be divided into joint bleeding, internal organ bleeding, mucocutaneous bleeding, and muscle/soft tissue hematomas. Hematomas can cause compression symptoms and signs. The definitive diagnosis of Hemophilia A relies on coagulation factor activity assays. Based on the level of this factor activity, Hemophilia A can be classified as mild, moderate, or severe. Hemophilia A should be differentiated from von Willebrand disease, acquired hemophilia, and hereditary coagulation factor XI deficiency. Prophylactic coagulation factor therapy is recommended for patients with this disease, especially severe cases, to reduce joint bleeding and subsequent dysfunction. Other prophylactic treatments should also be considered. In terms of treatment, supplementing the coagulation factor is the most effective measure to control bleeding in hemophilia. Mild or some moderate Hemophilia A patients may try desmopressin (DDAVP). Antifibrinolytic drugs can also be used. Complications of replacement therapy, namely the development of specific inhibitors to FVIII, should be managed promptly. Physical therapy and rehabilitation, management of hemophilic arthropathy, hemophilic pseudotumors, and blood-borne infections should also be given attention.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_HPL_B</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Hemophilia B</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_HPL_B_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Hemophilia is a group of inherited bleeding disorders caused by the reduction, absence, or dysfunction of coagulation factors, inherited in an X-linked recessive manner. Hemophilia B, also known as hereditary factor IX deficiency, has clinical manifestations identical to Hemophilia A, characterized by a positive family history, onset in childhood, uncontrollable bleeding after spontaneous or minor trauma, hematoma formation, and joint bleeding. It is a rarer type of hemophilia, with a much lower incidence than Hemophilia A. The symptoms are similar to those of Hemophilia A. The definitive diagnosis also relies on coagulation factor IX activity assays. In terms of treatment, replacement therapy is the mainstay, i.e., infusion of coagulation factor IX products or prothrombin complex concentrates. In the absence of these, fresh frozen plasma can be used. Prophylactic treatment is an important and standard part of care. In addition, antifibrinolytic drugs such as tranexamic acid are commonly used clinically, but these drugs are contraindicated in urinary tract bleeding and should be avoided in combination with prothrombin complex concentrates. Gene therapy offers a potential cure for hemophilia patients. Repeated infusions of recombinant coagulation factors or blood products in these patients can lead to the development of inhibitors and are often accompanied by allergic reactions, which should be noted.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_TCP</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Primary Immune Thrombocytopenia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_TCP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Primary immune thrombocytopenia, formerly known as idiopathic thrombocytopenic purpura, is a complex acquired autoimmune disease involving multiple mechanisms, accounting for about one-third of all bleeding disorders. It is the most common cause of isolated thrombocytopenia in clinical practice and can be seen in males and females of all ages. The clinical manifestations are mainly mucocutaneous bleeding, and in severe cases, internal organ bleeding may occur. The risk of bleeding increases with age. Some patients only have thrombocytopenia without bleeding symptoms. Some patients experience significant fatigue. It can be clinically divided into acute and chronic types, with the former being more common in children and the latter in adults. The etiology of this disease is not yet clear; infection, immune factors, the spleen, and other factors may be related. Clinically, the main manifestations are bleeding, a tendency for thrombosis, and fatigue. Blood tests may show a significantly reduced peripheral platelet count, and long-term anemia may also lead to normocytic anemia. Bleeding time is prolonged, and clot retraction is poor. Bone marrow aspiration is not essential for diagnosing this disease in adults (although it is designed this way in the module for gameplay mechanics). Most patients have detectable antibodies against platelet membrane glycoprotein complexes in their platelets or serum. The plateletcrit levels in patients are generally normal or near normal. This disease should be differentiated from anticoagulant-induced pseudothrombocytopenia, hereditary or congenital thrombocytopenia syndromes, drug-related thrombocytopenia, virus-related thrombocytopenia, secondary changes, and others. The goal of treatment is to raise the patient's platelet count to a safe level, reduce the risk of bleeding, and improve the quality of life. For patients who meet emergency treatment criteria, platelet transfusions, intravenous immunoglobulin, intravenous high-dose methylprednisolone, thrombopoietin receptor agonists, and recombinant human activated factor VII can be used. In critically ill patients, these treatments can be combined. The first-line treatment for newly diagnosed cases is glucocorticoids, commonly prednisone or dexamethasone. Studies have found that high-dose dexamethasone is faster-acting than standard-dose prednisone, has a lower incidence of adverse reactions, and a higher total effective rate and complete response rate. Intravenous immunoglobulin can also be used. Second-line treatments include thrombopoietin receptor agonists, anti-CD20 monoclonal antibodies, and splenectomy. Most patients have a good prognosis, with a mortality rate only slightly higher than the general population, although some are prone to relapse.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_HL</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Hodgkin Lymphoma</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_HL_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Hodgkin lymphoma (HL), also known as Hodgkin's disease, is a malignancy of the lymph nodes and lymphatic system. It is one of the most common malignancies in young adults and the most common type of lymphoma in Western developed countries. It can occur at any age but is more common in young adults. To date, its pathogenesis and etiology are not fully understood but may be related to genetic factors, Epstein-Barr virus, immunosuppression, ionizing radiation, and gene mutations. Its clinical manifestations mainly include superficial lymphadenopathy, fatigue, low-grade fever, and generalized pruritus (which often responds poorly to topical antipruritics or antihistamines). When enlarged lymph nodes compress adjacent tissues and organs, local compression symptoms such as a dry cough, abdominal pain, and lower limb edema may occur. Occasionally, patients may have symptomatic anemia or pancytopenia due to tumor invasion of the bone marrow. Asymptomatic splenomegaly may be present at diagnosis. Tissue biopsy (pathological examination) is the main basis for confirming the diagnosis of lymphoma. Hodgkin lymphoma has a high cure rate and was the first malignant tumor to be cured with chemotherapy. The common chemotherapy regimen for limited-stage disease is the ABVD regimen (this module uses this regimen: doxorubicin, vinblastine, bleomycin, and dacarbazine). For stages 3-4, a longer course of the ABVD regimen (commonly 4-6 cycles) or the BEACOPP regimen can be used. This should be combined with local radiotherapy.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_DLBCL</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Diffuse Large B-Cell Lymphoma</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_DLBCL_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Diffuse large B-cell lymphoma (DLBCL) accounts for approximately 32.5% of newly diagnosed non-Hodgkin lymphomas each year. It is more common in middle-aged and elderly males, with a slight male predominance. Sometimes the symptoms are insidious and go unnoticed, and it is often diagnosed at stage 3-4. Lymphoma is a malignant tumor of the lymph nodes and/or extranodal lymphoid tissues, belonging to the malignant diseases of the lymphohematopoietic system. Its occurrence is related to the malignant transformation of lymphocytes that proliferate and differentiate during the immune response, and it can occur in any part of the body. The specific pathogenesis is not yet clear, but infection and immune factors are considered important causes. In addition, genetic factors can increase the risk of developing the disease, and long-term use of immunosuppressants also increases the risk. Clinically, local symptoms include painless, progressive lymphadenopathy. Enlarged lymph nodes can compress surrounding tissues and organs, causing corresponding symptoms. 40-50% of patients present with extranodal disease, including the gastrointestinal tract, tonsils, oropharynx, liver, spleen, lungs, skin, soft tissues, bone marrow, and central nervous system. The gastrointestinal tract is the most common site of extranodal involvement, which can manifest as abdominal pain, bloating, and hematochezia. Systemic symptoms may include fever, weight loss, and night sweats. Some patients may have skin itching, fatigue, and weakness. 10%-20% of patients have bone marrow involvement, leading to anemia, leukocytosis or leukopenia, and thrombocytopenia. Laboratory tests may also show abnormalities such as an elevated erythrocyte sedimentation rate. The diagnosis of this disease is based on histopathology and classification. For treatment, patients are divided into two main categories: initial treatment and relapsed/refractory, with different treatment plans and strategies for each. Initially treated patients often receive different cycles of the R-CHOP regimen (rituximab, cyclophosphamide, doxorubicin, vincristine, and prednisone). In addition, there are other regimens with different uses, such as R-CEPP, R-CDOP, DHAP, and ESHAP.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_PNH</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Paroxysmal Nocturnal Hemoglobinuria</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_PNH_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Paroxysmal nocturnal hemoglobinuria (PNH) is an acquired hematopoietic stem cell clonal disease caused by a somatic mutation in the phosphatidylinositol glycan class A (PIGA) gene. The occurrence of intravascular hemolysis in patients shows a certain temporal relationship with sleep, hence the name. Clinical manifestations include hemoglobinuria, hematopoietic failure, thrombosis, and organ damage. In laboratory tests, blood counts may show normocytic anemia (but can be microcytic hypochromic in cases of iron deficiency). Bone marrow examination shows marked or active hyperplasia, with a predominance of the erythroid series. Intravascular hemolysis can also be seen. Flow cytometry is the gold standard for diagnosing this disease. In the past, the acid hemolysis test (Ham test) was often used as a classic confirmatory test, along with the sugar-water test, cobra venom factor hemolysis test, and heat hemolysis test. This disease needs to be differentiated from aplastic anemia, myelodysplastic syndrome, and other hemolytic anemias. In terms of supportive care, patients with severe anemia can be transfused with packed red blood cells. For controlling hemolytic episodes, in addition to avoiding factors such as diarrhea and colds, glucocorticoids can improve anemia in some patients and may reduce or alleviate hemolytic attacks. Antioxidant drugs were previously thought to have a protective effect on cell membranes, but their efficacy is uncertain. Patients with thrombosis should undergo thrombolysis and thrombectomy, with careful consideration of the risks and benefits. Standardized use of the anti-complement C5 monoclonal antibody, eculizumab, can make the survival time of patients comparable to that of the normal population, and the drug can also improve the natural course of the disease. There have been explorations of combined chemotherapy for refractory cases. Allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation can cure this disease. The survival period is relatively long, with a median of 10-15 years. The main causes of death are thrombosis, infection, and bleeding. Many patients have concurrent aplastic anemia. Transformation to myelodysplastic syndrome and acute leukemia is rare and has a poor prognosis.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_PMF</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Primary Myelofibrosis</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_PMF_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Primary myelofibrosis (PMF) is a rare disease with a global incidence of about 1 in 1.5 million. It sometimes develops from pre-existing polycythemia vera or essential thrombocythemia. It is a clonal proliferative disease originating from hematopoietic stem cells, causing inappropriate release of cytokines, leading to diffuse fibrosis of the bone marrow. This forces hematopoietic progenitor cells into the periphery, often accompanied by extramedullary hematopoiesis, primarily in the spleen, followed by the liver and lymph nodes. Typical clinical manifestations include leukoerythroblastosis, significant splenomegaly, varying degrees of osteosclerosis, and often a "dry tap" on bone marrow aspiration. The pathogenesis is not yet clear but may be related to excessive proliferation of megakaryocytes and the various cytokines they release. The disease often has an insidious onset and slow progression, and is frequently diagnosed incidentally upon discovery of an enlarged spleen. Many patients are asymptomatic or have non-specific symptoms at diagnosis. The main symptoms are divided into three aspects: early increase and later decrease of normal blood cells (often complicated by infection and bleeding), extramedullary hematopoiesis, and others (acute myelofibrosis similar to leukemia, kidney stones, liver cirrhosis, and symptoms of hypermetabolism). The blood picture shows moderate to severe normocytic anemia. Bone marrow aspiration often results in a "dry tap." Bone marrow biopsy is the main diagnostic basis. A typical X-ray finding is increased bone density. Currently, there is no specific therapy for this disease. If the patient is asymptomatic and blood counts are basically normal, no treatment is needed. The goal of general symptomatic treatment is to improve anemia and relieve compression symptoms caused by splenomegaly. First-line treatment at initial presentation may include a combination of androgens and glucocorticoids. Recombinant human erythropoietin (EPO) can be used for those with low erythropoietin levels. Ruxolitinib can be used for spleen reduction; previously, hydroxyurea or other myelosuppressive agents were also commonly used. Second-line treatments include radionuclide therapy or splenectomy. Targeted therapies such as thalidomide or lenalidomide can also be used. Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation is currently the only potentially curative method for this disease. The disease progresses slowly, and the course varies. Common causes of death are severe anemia, infection, heart failure, and bleeding, with a median survival of 2-5 years; a few can survive for more than 10 years. Those with an acute onset have a rapidly progressive course, usually less than one year. About 20% of patients eventually transform into acute myeloid leukemia.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_PV</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Polycythemia Vera</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_PV_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Polycythemia vera (PV) is a chronic myeloproliferative neoplasm primarily characterized by the abnormal proliferation of red blood cells, leading to an absolute increase in red blood cell mass, increased blood viscosity, often accompanied by elevated white blood cell and platelet counts, and splenomegaly. Complications such as bleeding or thrombosis may occur during the course of the disease. Clinical features include a ruddy complexion, hepatosplenomegaly, and vascular and neurological symptoms. Approximately 1 in 200,000 people are diagnosed with this disease each year, with a peak incidence between 50 and 60 years of age, making it a disease of middle to old age. Males are slightly more affected than females. The disease course can be divided into three stages. The pathogenesis is not yet fully understood, but it is known to be a clonal hematopoietic stem cell disorder originating from the pathological proliferation of a single hematopoietic stem cell. The onset is slow, and symptoms may not appear for several years, with some cases being discovered incidentally during a blood test. When blood volume and viscosity are significantly increased, the following clinical symptoms may occur. Neurological symptoms may appear early, with headache being the most common, accompanied by dizziness, fatigue, tinnitus, blurred vision, and memory loss. Later, there may be numbness and tingling in the extremities, excessive sweating, and visual disturbances. Plethoric manifestations may include a ruddy complexion. Some patients have hypertension or pruritus. A few may have ecchymoses and purpura. Thrombosis and embolism are common. Unless the disease is controlled, surgical procedures are generally not recommended. About 10-16% of patients have peptic ulcers, possibly related to increased histamine secretion. Extramedullary hematopoiesis can be seen, with splenomegaly, and the liver and lymph nodes may also be enlarged. A few cases may transform into acute leukemia, presenting with clinical manifestations of leukemia. Blood tests show increased red blood cell count and hemoglobin (which may be microcytic hypochromic due to iron deficiency). After the early stage, red blood cell morphology may change. About two-thirds of patients have an elevated white blood cell count, and the platelet count is usually higher than normal. Bone marrow biopsy showing significant fibrosis is one of the important qualitative criteria. Blood volume and viscosity also show corresponding changes. The disease needs to be differentiated from other diseases or conditions that cause an increase in red blood cells. First-line treatment includes symptomatic management, thrombosis prevention, phlebotomy, or therapeutic erythrocytapheresis. Cytoreductive therapy commonly uses hydroxyurea or interferon-alpha. Second-line treatments include radionuclide therapy, alkylating agents, and targeted therapy. If there are no serious complications, the disease progresses slowly. Without treatment, the average survival is only 18 months. With treatment, which is often slow to take effect, patients can survive for 10-15 years or more.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_FL</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Follicular Lymphoma</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_FL_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Follicular lymphoma is the second most common type of non-Hodgkin lymphoma and the most common type of indolent lymphoma. Follicular lymphoma originates from germinal center B-cells. The disease is more common in the elderly, with a median age of 55-60 years, and slightly more common in females. The main clinical manifestation is painless, slow-growing lymphadenopathy, especially in superficial areas. Bone marrow involvement is present in about 70% of cases, while visceral involvement is not common. Less than 20% of patients have B symptoms such as fever, night sweats, and fatigue. The diagnosis of follicular lymphoma depends on an adequate specimen, preferably an excisional biopsy of a tumor mass or lymph node. In terms of treatment, involved-field radiotherapy is one of the recommended treatment options for newly diagnosed cases. For patients with systemic symptoms or high tumor burden requiring systemic therapy, rituximab (R) combined with chemotherapy is the currently recommended first-line choice. R-CHOP or RB (rituximab and bendamustine) regimens are commonly used. Clinical studies have shown little difference in the objective response rate (ORR) between the two. Many scholars hope to treat this disease with non-cytotoxic drugs alone (rituximab combined with lenalidomide, RR regimen), but the long-term survival and adverse reactions of this regimen are not clear, and it requires greater financial cost, so it should be chosen with caution.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_vWD</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>von Willebrand Disease</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_vWD_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>von Willebrand disease is a hereditary bleeding disorder caused by a deficiency of von Willebrand factor, mostly inherited in an autosomal dominant manner. The incidence reported in other countries is about 0.1% to 1%. It is clinically characterized by a bleeding tendency from a young age, prolonged bleeding time, decreased platelet adhesion function, defective ristocetin-induced platelet aggregation, and a deficiency or structural abnormality of von Willebrand factor antigen. Acquired forms of the disease are mostly associated with underlying diseases, but a few may occur without any. Although a bleeding tendency is a prominent feature of this disease, its bleeding characteristics are different from those of hemophilia. It affects both males and females, with bleeding mainly involving the skin and mucous membranes. The bleeding tendency may decrease with age. Spontaneous joint and muscle bleeding are rare, and resulting disability is also uncommon. Bleeding screening tests are often normal or show only a prolonged APTT. For those with one or more abnormal diagnostic test results for von Willebrand factor antigen, typing confirmatory tests are performed. The goal of treatment is to correct the bleeding and coagulation abnormalities. Mild, asymptomatic patients do not require treatment and should avoid trauma and surgery, as well as drugs that affect platelet function. Those with bleeding can be treated with desmopressin, plasma products containing von Willebrand factor, recombinant von Willebrand factor, and antifibrinolytic drugs.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_MCL</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Mantle Cell Lymphoma</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_MCL_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Mantle cell lymphoma (MCL) is a rare subtype of mature B-cell non-Hodgkin lymphoma that has gradually become a curable or controllable lymphoma subtype in recent years. It is currently believed that the cells of this disease can originate from pre-germinal center B-cells, or from activated B-cells that have undergone antigen stimulation post-germinal center. The disease is more common in the elderly, and over 80% of patients are diagnosed at a late stage, presenting with lymphadenopathy, hepatosplenomegaly, and bone marrow involvement. Other common sites of extranodal involvement are the gastrointestinal tract and Waldeyer's ring. Some patients may have significant lymphocytosis, similar to chronic lymphocytic leukemia. Most patients have a relatively acute onset and an aggressive course, but some present with manifestations similar to a chronic lymphoproliferative disease with an indolent course, presenting in a leukemic form. The diagnosis of this disease relies on pathological examination. In terms of treatment, classic MCL should be treated immediately after diagnosis. For late-stage patients (stage 1-2 patients are extremely rare) who are not suitable for autologous hematopoietic stem cell transplantation, rituximab combined with chemotherapy, such as the R-CHOP regimen (rituximab, cyclophosphamide, vincristine, doxorubicin, and prednisone), is often used. Newer drugs such as ibrutinib, bortezomib, and lenalidomide are also available. Over the past 30 years, great progress has been made in both the research of its pathogenesis and clinical treatment, gradually entering the molecular era. However, this disease is still an incurable tumor, especially for high-risk groups or patients with specific genetic abnormalities, for whom effective treatment methods are still lacking.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_HCL</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Hairy Cell Leukemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_HEM_HCL_DESC</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Hairy cell leukemia (HCL) is a rare, indolent B-cell lymphoproliferative disorder. The tumor cells primarily infiltrate the bone marrow and spleen, followed by the liver and lymph nodes. Patients often present with weight loss, fatigue, hepatosplenomegaly, pancytopenia, and recurrent infections. This disease is divided into two different clinical types: classic and variant. The cause of this disease is still unknown. It is more common in middle-aged and elderly people, with a median age of onset of 55 years and a male-to-female ratio of 4:1. The most common symptoms are abdominal distension, fatigue, and weight loss. Physical examination often reveals hepatosplenomegaly, while superficial lymphadenopathy is rare. Anemia, bleeding, and infection are also common symptoms. Skin and central nervous system infiltration, lytic bone lesions, and splenic rupture have all been reported. A complete blood count may show pancytopenia, or cytopenia in two or one lineage. Hairy cells can be detected on a peripheral blood smear. Bone marrow examination shows hairy cell infiltration, and bone marrow aspiration often results in a "dry tap." This disease should be differentiated from chronic lymphocytic leukemia, splenic marginal zone lymphoma, etc. Treatment should be initiated when systemic symptoms are significant, the spleen is markedly enlarged causing compression symptoms, or there are recurrent infections. Purine analogs are commonly used to treat this disease. Fludarabine was used initially, but cladribine is now the first choice to reduce the adverse drug reaction of pancytopenia. Pentostatin has similar efficacy but is not yet available in China. In addition, bendamustine combined with rituximab also has good efficacy. Interferon-alpha can achieve long-term disease control, but complete remission is rare. Splenectomy is no longer advocated for patients with this disease unless there is a special need. Treatment with purine analogs has significantly improved the prognosis, with a complete remission rate of over 90% and a long duration of remission. Opportunistic infections are the main cause of death in this disease.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	</LocalizedStrings>
  </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
