<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<Database>
  <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_MOD_OPHTHALMOLOGY_DIAGNOSES">
    <LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
    <LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
    <Contributors>
      <Name>WDZRMPCBIT</Name>
    </Contributors>
    <LocalizedStrings>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_DRYEYE</LocID>
        <Text>Dry Eye Disease</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_DRYEYE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Corneal and conjunctival dryness and discomfort caused by decreased tear secretion or stability, common in overuse of eyes or tear film abnormalities.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_RRD</LocID>
        <Text>Retinal Detachment</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_RRD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Separation of the photosensitive cell layer from the pigment epithelium due to retinal tears or traction, often presenting as flashes, floaters, and a curtain-like shadow.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_IRITIS</LocID>
        <Text>Anterior Uveitis</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_IRITIS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Predominantly inflammation of the iris and ciliary body, presenting with ciliary congestion, photophobia, eye pain, and decreased vision. Slit-lamp examination reveals anterior chamber cells and flare.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_CATARACT</LocID>
        <Text>Cataract</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_CATARACT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Painless decrease in vision caused by lens opacity, may be accompanied by glare, poor night vision, and refractive changes. Diagnosis can be confirmed by slit-lamp examination.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_AMD</LocID>
        <Text>Age-Related Macular Degeneration</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_AMD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>A degenerative disease affecting the macular area, presenting with decreased central vision and metamorphopsia. OCT/fluorescein angiography may reveal neovascularization or leakage.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_HORDEOLUM</LocID>
        <Text>Hordeolum</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_HORDEOLUM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Acute purulent inflammation of the eyelid margin, often seen as a localized small nodule with redness, swelling, and pain, which may develop a pustule.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_DR</LocID>
        <Text>Diabetic Retinopathy (Mild)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_DR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Retinal microvascular disease caused by glucose metabolism disorder. Fundoscopy reveals microaneurysms, hemorrhages, and exudates. Macular edema can lead to decreased vision.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_HSV_KERATITIS</LocID>
        <Text>Herpes Simplex Keratitis</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_HSV_KERATITIS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Caused by herpes virus infection of the cornea, characterized by dendritic ulcers upon fluorescein staining, accompanied by eye pain, photophobia, and lacrimation.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_MGD</LocID>
        <Text>Meibomian Gland Dysfunction</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_MGD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Dry eye symptoms caused by abnormal secretion of the meibomian glands, presenting with eye discomfort, a burning sensation, and fluctuating vision. Examination reveals blocked meibomian gland orifices.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_CSCR</LocID>
        <Text>Central Serous Chorioretinopathy</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_CSCR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Subretinal fluid accumulation caused by choroidal vascular leakage, presenting with blurred central vision and metamorphopsia. OCT reveals fluid accumulation.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_PTERYGIUM</LocID>
        <Text>Pterygium</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_PTERYGIUM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>A triangular proliferation of conjunctival tissue growing towards the cornea, common with long-term ultraviolet exposure, may cause blurred vision or a sensation of irritation.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_DACRYOCYSTITIS</LocID>
        <Text>Dacryocystitis</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_DACRYOCYSTITIS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Redness, swelling, and pain caused by infection of the lacrimal sac, may be accompanied by purulent discharge, and is often caused by nasolacrimal duct obstruction.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_PTOSIS</LocID>
        <Text>Ptosis</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_PTOSIS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Abnormally low position of the upper eyelid, which may affect the visual field and appearance, common in neurological or muscular diseases.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_ENTROPION</LocID>
        <Text>Entropion</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_ENTROPION_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Inward turning of the eyelid margin, where eyelashes may irritate the cornea, leading to discomfort and inflammation.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_ECTROPION</LocID>
        <Text>Ectropion</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_ECTROPION_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Outward turning of the eyelid margin, which may lead to poor tear drainage and conjunctival exposure, causing dryness and irritation.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_ORBITAL_CELLULITIS</LocID>
        <Text>Orbital Cellulitis</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_ORBITAL_CELLULITIS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Infection of the orbital soft tissues, presenting with eyelid swelling, pain, fever, and decreased vision, possibly accompanied by proptosis.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_MYOPIA</LocID>
        <Text>Myopia</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_MYOPIA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Distant objects are blurry while near objects are clear, caused by an excessively long eyeball or excessive corneal curvature.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_AMBLYOPIA</LocID>
        <Text>Amblyopia</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_AMBLYOPIA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Decreased vision in one or both eyes due to abnormal visual development, typically when not treated in a timely manner during childhood.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_KERATOCONUS</LocID>
        <Text>Keratoconus</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_KERATOCONUS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>The central part of the cornea bulges outward into a cone shape, which may cause blurred vision and photophobia.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_PVD</LocID>
        <Text>Posterior Vitreous Detachment</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_PVD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Posterior detachment caused by liquefaction and contraction of the vitreous, common in the elderly, may cause symptoms of flashes and floaters.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_CHALAZION</LocID>
        <Text>Chalazion</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_CHALAZION_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>A painless lump formed by chronic inflammation of a meibomian gland, usually located on the upper or lower eyelid, which may resolve on its own or require surgical removal.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_DR_SEVERE</LocID>
        <Text>Diabetic Retinopathy (Severe)</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_DR_SEVERE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Severe retinal disease caused by diabetes, characterized by numerous microaneurysms, hemorrhages, and exudates, which can lead to severe vision loss.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_CHOROIDITIS</LocID>
        <Text>Choroiditis</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_CHOROIDITIS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Inflammation of the choroid, which may be caused by infection, immune reactions, or other diseases, presenting with blurred vision, photophobia, and eye pain.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_VITRITIS</LocID>
        <Text>Vitritis</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_VITRITIS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Inflammation within the vitreous cavity, which may be caused by infection, immune reactions, or other diseases, presenting with blurred vision, floaters, and eye pain.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>

      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_OPTIC_NEURITIS</LocID>
        <Text>Optic Neuritis</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>DIA_OPH_OPTIC_NEURITIS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>
        <Text>Inflammation of the optic nerve, which may be caused by infection, immune reactions, or other diseases, presenting with decreased vision, abnormal color vision, and eye pain.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
    </LocalizedStrings>
  </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
